It's late after show
Star shine is so bright watch the secret Sun fold
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what
we are came
I've been missing in my sleep
Hi guys, what's up?
Hello.
Let's see if I can get the slider to work one more time.
No.
Hi, how are you doing?
Take you to the kitchen.
So my fricking tripod.
The thing that took the head detachment. I like got a masking tape to put up. Sorry, my kitchen
Finally clean, okay, so it's not holding it up in any way so
Oh, oh shit, and oh i'm getting new glasses today too. I wonder if they might be here soon
But I have these for the time being
Yeah, but look, this is what I used to hold up my thing and so it broke, right?
It's like, it's like, it's like screws in there. Sorry.
But it's, I mean, without managing it without the tape, right?
Screws in, but it's like, it won't screw in anymore or hold in there anymore.
But maybe, what should I do? Maybe I should put tape around the...
The thing like the inside it and like maybe we'll like stay. I don't know. I don't know but it won't hold or anything. Hey, yeah
But I know well, I think I was pretty hold I like the AI song that guys I was so expensive to make that video
I think I cost probably
well
You know
It uses these credits and I didn't know.
I thought I was just gonna make unlimited videos for me.
I paid like 20 bucks for the membership.
So I was like, you know, I mean,
I put through the thing for that video
because it makes it in like two seconds.
It just had to do it in like two seconds.
It comes up with a whole storyboard and everything.
I didn't go through it, which I should have, right?
Because there's like weird stuff.
It's some weird stuff in the video.
Did I sleep well?
Does it look like it?
I did.
Yeah, there's a little bit. There's not like that much weird stuff, but there's like
Like so there's someone hiding in the bushes and it's like this weird
Androgynous being like hiding in the bushes like watching them and then at the very end like page has
I don't know it was weird
Some of it was weird and I can't fix it okay, I can but it's like okay, but I'll tell you so
So then I paid the 20 bucks and I was like making the video and then it stopped like halfway through
And it's like oh well, it's like you're out of credits. You have to buy more credit
I'm like oh shit, so it and it's like I paid another 15 bucks for like
600 credits
I think he used like 300 and something he's like almost 400 of them and then so I have like 200 left
So I made and so basically I've spent like $35 so far and I have and that's I have that video, but
And I want to have I wanted to make it the more like the show. I don't know
I just thought that was cute. That was like I just had made them in that day
I guess and it was cute, but I think it is a cute. It's a cute video, you know
I guess the replay value will be, I don't know,
maybe I'll end the show with it occasionally, but yeah.
But that's a really cool, what AI can do
because it's like, basically I use like three or four
AI things in conjunction to make that together.
It'd be great if I'm serving up.
I mean, if Alexander wasn't such a dick.
And then last night, Alexander was like,
oh, play this certain song.
Like he was so mean about the video too.
He's like, what the?
he's just like such a such an asshole okay so guys so the panels today like we have some panels i
think we have like two um we have two panels paid for already or sponsored right and so as soon as
like those people like i think it is i'm going to be jamie's cowboys and um summer
Okay, and some more once whenever she calls when she wants to do the panel, like, you know, she'll let me know.
And then Jamie can let me know whenever it's, you know, she wants me to use that one. Okay.
And then, yeah, otherwise, you know, you can purchase a, or sponsor a panel.
I'm thinking like, you know, I'll probably do like two panels a show
About I mean and then the spot I mean, I'll still bring on guests one-on-one, but
If it's because I do I want to do readings one-on-one. And so, you know, so I'll do like, you know
If you want to come up for a read, you know a reading and stuff like that or just chat and stuff like that one-on-one
I'm happy to do that
But and but I know people loved his like hang out with different people and like, you know
I'm not really good with groups and so but it is you know, it's fun for people and I think people really like it
It's one of the most popular parts of the show. So of course and of course I love the different personalities and it's like having guests
Um, so, um, yeah, so I'm, I'm going to be having the panel sponsor and also I will put the sponsor on the banner throughout the whole time the panel is up and it's just that it's just one person has to sponsor it or you can cut, you know, people can like say, oh, I'll do five bucks, you do five bucks or something like that.
You can send it either Super Chat, Cash App,
and then it's just a way to basically,
to keep the show growing, I would say,
because I'm spending a lot of money.
I need to buy a brand new fucking tripod.
I need to, I have a lot of stuff I wanna do.
Best bought a bunch of new cords for my phone. So I should be able to like move further around the room
I've been unfortunately, you know, you know tripod here. So tomorrow
You can put this actually in the little case and put it up somewhere
So guys, I so you know
I don't know anything about TikTok I know like those people on it like and then she's like all it is to me is a
Bunch of camera filters, but you know Emma. Oh and oh gosh for the Alistair showed up
Okay, Emma was on TikTok. She had 23,000 subscribers
I was like and then you know and you can make or people are making money because you can monetize
I don't know if a lot of people know about it or like you can create the content even if they use the subscribers
But I can but I can start putting like kind of decent content on there. I think oops
Yeah, I bought a new tempo about oops I bought a new game
I did buy a new cord about
Because they're really good quality and they're like long and I have about like there's a couple of them
Amazon is pretty good deals of them. Oh, there's by probably at Amazon. Oh
Yeah, oh
Okay, that keeps her now. Yeah
But uh
But it's good. It's also like also the with the panel thing. It's like
You know some of it I
Just I feel it's something that should be sponsored
I also feel that they're like really really good panels and
That and people so far far been very happy to is the bot working you try nothing shows
Yeah, it looks like it see home. Let me see what happens
Yeah, I see it sassy. Do you see it?
You have a blocked accidentally. Hey, happy birthday Nick Johnson. Hey, Crystal Marie. How are you?
Can Tom flash come up when he's done you? Yes, he can. Yeah, we can do one one. I also want to thank Alexandra
Myers
I'm so sorry Alexandra
What a great guest yesterday, what a pleasant I what a pleasant
Surprise meeting you and thank you very much. Yeah, I got you know what you said this morning. Thank you so much
then you know, thank you so much. I really appreciate that and
Really cool
Thank you
Very awesome person. Hey, what's up? Nobody? Hey, Jonathan guys. By the way, we're at over a hundred members members of the channel
You know, thanks to many, many of you have renewed it and thank you so much for renewing it.
And many have received some gift members since I gave, I did definitely, I gave like five away
yesterday or five or six. Hopefully, yeah, I think I'll maybe give away a couple tonight, you know.
I like to keep the ranks, keep up the ranks to the Psyche's Angels ranks as, you know, we got some really cool people.
Hey, New York native.
Guys, I also have the emojis updated for the members. You can see New York native has, he's using the I emoji.
I also have like a, I have like a, I have an old lady emoji.
I don't know what that is. I don't know. It's just a funny picture.
I have like, it says LOL, it says SOS.
It says different things.
Yeah, there's the grandma.
She could be our little chat grandma watching over things.
Okay, so, oh, hey, what's up, New York native?
And yeah, so what else yeah, so but I do want to wait for your Jamie's Cowboys or
Summer to like let me know that they'd like to
Start the panel that they they have sponsored. I want the people to be able to be here. Hey Vanguard
But yeah, Tom Flashin, yeah, I'll talk to him.
Yeah, it's just gonna be one-on-one, you know?
It's like, unless someone would like to open the panel
beyond that, unless Summer or Jamie comes in
and wants to start it, you know?
Well, then somebody else can sponsor it.
And I'll put up the banner because there's no,
let me see,
let me see, sponsor the panel.
Yeah, so there it is.
For about it's approximately three hours. I may I might fiddle around with the pricing or the
Time I think it might be like I don't know but I may I try to leave it. Thank you crystal
Yeah, and it just will keep it like probably more
You know the people what like when I like you know not waste time like you know
behave better, hopefully, or at least the person that's that sponsors the panel will be like, hey, you know
You know, that's an ownership in the in it too and we'll help to bend it and stuff. So thank you, Chris
I appreciate that
You like that and that's my tattoo. I'll be KG when that's my tattoo in New York, Native
So, yeah, I was a my tattoos on there and
And also I should be able to put some more up now.
So guys, if you have an idea for an emoji,
like that you'd like member, especially a member,
if you'd like to have an idea for an emoji,
just let me know.
Because, oh, oh, so Vanguard injected, yeah.
So, oops, sorry.
Okay, so just.
Oops, okay, so this reminds you I
What are the commands bug plug and but whole yeah?
Can you get different eyes? Yeah, I can I can look at some
So I just was using some clip art. I can't get some different eyes
You are you what you want more eyes or just different ones? I
Think I can update any any of the emojis. I just have to you know shrink down. I have some graphics programs and stuff
Yep
So, how many chromosomes is a human body?
I'm not sure.
I'd be a DSDB.
Oh, okay.
So, I'm just saying, I'm just saying in Vanguard, but we will be one-on-one, right?
It'll be one-on-one.
Nobody else can come on the panel until it's sponsored, you know, and there are a couple
sponsored, but I want to make sure that the sponsor is here before I start their, their
sponsored panels.
When your panel is going that you sponsor, there's, you get advertisements, oops, the
And so it's a good way to promote too, if you'd like to promote some of the show.
Okay, so shit, I don't know what's wrong with this bucket.
Oh yeah, so I put it up.
Okay, so here's Vanguard.
Okay, let me just make sure.
Also, it's easier to keep track of like, you know, for more.
Good evening there Mr. Loevely cut psyche. Oh, hi. How are you?
It's your Sunday being cope aesthetic it's so far
Pretty good. It's not bad. I'm just
Hanging out, you know, it's like a cat around here. Yeah, the tricks is right. Oh, who's this Lola Lola right here, huh?
You sleeping Lola
That's miss Lola sleeping over here
What a lovely lovely cat
Hi
It's sitting over there, but I don't know where the other cats are the cats are around
I can appreciate cats. I love cats, but I'm not a cat person, you know, I mean
yeah well you know some people a lot of people are allergic to cats and some
people are just like not cat people cats can be kind of aloof sometimes so I
like that yeah so but I think big the yeah I think they're it can be very
very sweet some cats are aloof like it's like I've had some aloof cats you know
that are like kind of like they just like are one of you more like outside or
like walking around and but I like like a lot of the cats are like you know
Trick. Yeah, Lola. They're sweet. They're like the inside
Cats are lovely dogs are lovely, but they can all be dicks the same as humans
But we've all seen the YouTube videos
Because the internet is about cats these days and dickheads on the internet
The cats are cunts and they're fucking on that's the bosses and the swipe this the swipe that
Come on, we've all seen those nasty cat videos, I think.
Well, I mean, you know, cat women, the cat burger, I mean, there's certain associations with cats,
but it's a very fair to like, you know, blame cats for anything.
We always tend to like put our negative qualities into the animals, but they're our own human qualities.
The cats aren't really doing anything. The cats are just being cats.
It's very negative when the YouTube, sorry, the internet validity is not just about humans
destroying others, but it's nice cat videos to make you feel happy and also, what?
It was like, it used to be like the LOL cats and like the memes and stuff like that.
And there was like, they're not really like, I mean, it's like, some of them are funny
as popular as they were, but I love having cats on my show, you know.
Do you hear that supposedly people with cats develop dementia? Okay, yeah, there's something called
Toxoplasma, sorry, Toxoplasmosis. Toxoplasmosis comes from cat poo and dog poo, and it only affects
It doesn't only affect pregnant women. I've heard it. It can affect the brain of people. I probably have it
You know, it's like I think it is pretty common actually too. Okay, so link snatch whoever that is that the panel is
The panel is closed or hold on one second
Right, yeah, you can hang up at the station. It's fine. You can wait. I'll have you on after I have introduced myself
I've not been so offensive, but we've had a good joke about cats the loveliness how the internet works with cats
Etc etc etc
It can be from like, you know, from using the cat, a cat box and having like something on their paws and then like, you know, walking on your dishes and then you put, you know, so you have to be kind of careful with like just like letting them walk all over like certain things that you like, you know, eat, but I don't think.
Mean and I know I mean I think it might be like overblown a little bit because it's like trying to say
Oh, it's like a zone like a zombie like a virus like the cats are spreading and they're making people docile
Toxy plasmosis as you call it only affects pregnant women
Okay, well, that's that I think you think if like the tampon thing there's something called like toxemia or something
There's something women get like
It's dog poo and cat poo apparently
But, do you know what? A cat can shit anywhere, but a dog can't. What?
A dog can or can't sit anywhere?
A dog, a dog on society says you must pick up your dog poo, but a cat shit anywhere.
Yeah, but no, the cats don't just shit anywhere, they bury their waste because they don't like the smell of it.
So they bury it, you know, so they're actually like a very like, you know, you know, putting the earth and stuff,
which is, and that's what my cats do most of the time.
Yeah, mate, mate, I'm not having a goat cat here, but what I am having a goat.
is you will be fined if your dog shits and you don't pick it up but a cat can shit anywhere
and nobody has a problem with that. It doesn't fit on shit anywhere they usually will bury it
that's what I'm saying it's like did you ever see cats shit just like like all around the
game ground do you see people like you know leaving cats shit on the ground no it's like
I mean maybe rarely right so you haven't had cats foreign cats shitting in your garden before
No, I've had raccoons have I had raccoons shit on the roof across the way, but not not a cat
They bury it. I never know where they put it. Let's not make it all about nuts, but Toxi plus Moses
But it's supposed to only affect pregnant women apparently
Only affect pregnant women. Well, yeah, I don't know. I have to look more into it
I don't I maybe it does. I heard it affected the brain somehow. I don't know. I'm not sure I'm not a doctor
And so I can't give any medical advice about it. No, hey, what's up tricks? Come on. There's tricks
I should come over tricks and say hi
Trixie hello tricks
Hey
Yeah, okay. Well, anyway, so I got some new decks. It's new tarot decks. They're pretty cool and
You know, I started this new this new panel idea
Which I think is working really really well, especially because now I get to talk more one-on-one to people and then and that or otherwise
You know, I have a bit exciting, you know sponsored panel going that's cool. Yeah, keeping the cat box clean. Yeah
Okay, that's almost all the cats find the cats are very well fed. They're very happy. They're very satisfied. There's a nice
Plenty of food. Um, your cuts do look very happy. Well, don't
Thank you. Yeah, they are very happy cats, but
It's uh, there's a lot of them here. And so it's like the ones that are here get along with each other basically and you put this
My cord in yeah, so let me plug in this cord. So have you been it's it's been a little few few
Few weeks. I think since I spoke into you. So
It's pretty quite hot it's been quite exhausting, but I am doing daily life
You understand what I mean? Just living
Doing the daily life. Yeah, I hear you. Oh, my tablet was upside down. Okay, so now I can charge it. Yeah
Sorry, I'm just charging my tablet so I can oh
Evil five guys
dear evil five
How nice to see you evil five guys nice to see you
Okay, I'm just looking, I'm just checking to see if my glasses are here. Hold on one second
Yeah, it says between 430 and 730 tonight, okay, so okay, so let me see if I can put this down. There we go
Uh-oh. Yeah. Let's go. So, Katnip, evil five guys, evil, I'm not talking to you, uh, Psych.
Um, I'm talking to evil five guys. Do you know who evil five guys is?
Is he in the chat?
Yeah, he's called Evil Ronald McDonald but he's really evil five times.
Is that the same? I've met Ronald McDonald in, but that's like Evil Ronald McDonald. Hey, Crystal.
Evil five guys.
Is it evil? Is it evil Ron McDonald redundant? Like Ron McDonald is a really creepy clown with like bright red hair
And then he like practices magic. Do you remember you believe in magic and then you know McDonald's is of course the response
But can I just put this shiner on the caveat, please have you ever smoked catnip before?
No, I just smoke weed. Well, yeah, I smoke catnip, of course. You know, big deal
It's I mean, it's like not great. It didn't really get me that high. I don't think I'm you know
I'm more into like, you know
Weed
That's like it. No, it's like
Joker's like I would like to answer the catnip in the night. He's like it's so high man
Yeah
But evil McDonald Ronald five guys just said he's gonna get Billy on me
Billy like more at Billy
Not that one, right? Not more at Billy. I don't know who Billy is then. All I know is the more at Billy
Is that his name?
That's the one
Okay, no
Uh-oh, yeah
Well, so let's see you are not a large human if you use a tiny roller. Oh, okay
Yeah, we're twenty-three people in chat. So just so are you down for a little card reading or no?
Yes, I'm up for a bit card reading. Who do you want to make cards for for you?
But I'm just like but I'm saying okay, so I have like I have like five decks you could choose from okay
So you can choose either the rainbow tarot alien tarot
Monster Tarot?
No, no, no, my cards have already been read, so let's read people in the chat's cards.
No, people in the, well, I will, I mean I will, but I'd prefer to read them out, but your cards have already been read, so you don't want to read.
Well, my cards, my cards have already been read, you know that, come on.
We know because I don't believe things are written in the future. Oh, I mean one of your best fucking
Persons, I love that prairie person. She's lovely and she read my card so beautifully the other day
Okay, perfect. Oh, yeah, I understand then you know, you never need you don't need another car. Oh, yeah, yeah
No, if you Tony the conductor start and see here, let me know
Who's hosting the open panel?
This is not, the panel guest is Vanguard.
It's done open panel, it's just one-on-one.
Vanguard probably has another like three minutes.
But I'll just, I'm just doing one-on-one talks until,
but Jamie's Cowboys and Summer both have a panel,
a sponsored panel coming up
that we'll probably be having theirs today.
Hey, Spunky, how are you?
Um, but I have my new cards, but anyway, yeah, okay. Well
Yeah, yeah, isn't a crystal. Okay, so, um, yeah, yeah
Anything else?
Uh, I just wonder how you recycle beer. That's all I'm asking
Recycle what?
Yeah, look at evil five guys
And I'm just questioning, how do you recycle beer?
Okay.
Well, of course, hold on.
Well, why don't you go into the chat and go to chat in there, and I'll do some readings
for the chat.
Thank you.
Okay.
You're welcome.
Anyway, thank you Mrs. Doubtfire for calling in. Okay, okay, so who says a card?
Ninja with a pencil. Yeah, I'll pull a card. I'll pull an alien card for you
Yeah, sponsored panels next it works a lot better. It's a lot more fun. It really is
Works much better
because
Panels really do take they are they're taking a large part of portion of the show I
Like I like to do readings one-on-one. I like to do one-on-one chat
I don't like it to have bunch of people on the panel take over and they go. Oh, yeah, we take over the show
so
You have
Sponsors
I'm a Capricorn. I'm into I'm into business. Oh good. It's gracious
I pay for streamer
But I saw I didn't seem to you was very upset with me. He's like it was the whole show the show is called
hey, hey me to talk to me or something like that and
I mean, we ever heard of sponsorships guys and we heard of like having a sponsor
That's what it is. You see how it's like, you know, I
Have a banner on my screen that I can advertise to and people can like people will go and subscribe to places
I don't understand if people know the concept of commercials or that kind of thing. I keep things pretty
like, not too intrusive on the show.
Like, I'm not like starting to do these paid product placements
and stuff like that.
I'm like just, you know, advertising the community.
And allowing people, and I always advertise,
I allow free advertising.
Everything that I offer, I offer like a free version of it,
right?
You're of course welcome to post your own link in the chat if you'd like to or ask them on if they kid if you're trying to build a
Build a panel or something like that or build a channel. I will help you for free
But
It's a plan demand when there's a demand when there's a demand for my panels people seem to want to chat with people on my show and talk to me and
I'd like to
Continue to do it, but sometimes it's very time-consuming and
Need to wait find a way to monetize it. Okay. I'm sorry. So ninja with a pencil
Four of swords
Yeah, it's like I think good
You have to be like, examine something very carefully.
There's something with communication, let me see.
Yeah, there's like somebody that really wants to work
with you, I think it's like, or a soulmate kind of thing.
I don't know, I think that this is like,
do you have this person?
but also like really trying to stay balanced.
Okay, yeah, I don't know, what's your, what's your size?
Oh, shit, ah!
This almost looks like the ninja,
kind of like this, this is gotta like,
I think it's like the, I don't know,
he looks like a kind of like alien ninja a little bit to me.
That's your ninja with a pencil.
So you might have a lot of this Knight of Swords energy.
Knight of Swords.
You know really good talker really fast. We'll really go rush in rush out
Get hurt feelings argumentative oh
Thank you, I see where I'll give you word advice though. I think it's like, you know
Yeah, I mean it's like I'm not I'm just not gonna put that person's picture up the okay
So it looks like the world the advice is like
To complete the cycle. There's like it looks like the cycle will be completed
There's like an end to something a beginning of something else
Also, I would say completeness recognized like because the world is everything physically. This is the world is everything and so we are basically
We are all the fool through the world all the cards, you know, but and those are all the the journey
But we will all take that journey
But this is just the beginning of a new journey though. It looks like almost like going into a new a
New dimension or something like that. We're kind of like finally coming through or something
If you like that anybody else I'll do another deck of these decks are like from
You know Etsy I can actually get the
Get the book I sometimes like to have the art like the author's interpretation because sometimes they have their own idea about
Things and the cards can be very different sometimes
Okay
Right and so it's like
That's why it's easier to read on a writer a writer deck
This is a little bit alien to me that resonated with you. Oh, awesome. I
Was wondering the same thing sassy the YouTube has new rules. Okay. We're talking about the the monetizing rules. We talked about
They don't want I guess they don't want people just using all generated content
Like I think you're still allowed to use generated content. That'd be crazy if you because there's AI being used in a lot of things, right?
So I'll be right back
It's literally like you kids like
There's a only fans account
There's an only fans account that makes like I think like a hundred thousand dollars or more a month and all it does is use
AI generated porn. I have never heard that
Do I find you attractive Doug?
Yeah
who is that? I don't know who that is. Okay, so yeah, so AI porn. So it is, I mean, it's
like, okay, well, there's a bunch of famous streamers that already have like their people
can just do face swapping. And so basically, it's like a normal porn. And then they put,
you know, do the AI, it takes out the person's face, and it just puts the other person's
Yeah, there's the AI, but so it basically that's just already poor, but then it's like when it gets to the generated
It's like yeah, you can't even tell the difference right here. It's like it's just
No, what was it? Oh shit
Oh, you're talking about the, oh, the butt in the chat.
Okay, yeah, that PBL Rufi, I put his picture
accidentally on me before.
Like they're saying, they're saying it's like,
oh, you can show, as long as you're not explicit.
There's also, I mean, the nudity policy is very confusing.
It's all about, you can show like,
Nudity in certain things if it's like educational if you're like showing how to wax of a Jaina you're allowed
I mean
I think you're allowed to do that like you're allowed to show it or something like that
It's always like it's weird like you're allowed to do different things, but you can't just do it for like sex for like
Like, you know, it can't it gets it can't be too sexy or something
So anyway
But yeah, so this AI-generated poor makes a lot of money, right?
And so it's like, there's people that have their whole channels or just pure AI is just
running the channel.
They'll just do these AI-generated, and it's like, some of these are better than others,
right?
Can you do a quick alien reading?
Sure, New York native.
Like a quick alien reading.
Okay, absolutely.
Alien tarot.
Yeah.
Are you talking about the nudity? Yeah, I would say it's like you have to put it, you know
Put it under just for adults and stuff like that
I mean there I have seen that they're more explicit stuff so you can just put it under under like a
But all it does is ask you. Oh, are you 18? Okay, I'm just playing for you in New York native
Yeah, it has to be labeled as scientific. Yeah
Okay, okay
Okay, I'm an advice for New York native. Okay. Okay. Oh, okay
Yes, okay
So we start with the we start with this second this two of wands and this is kind of like, you know
And this is another kind of bringing a card about bringing your
your
Focus, you know your powers together with another person, but I also this looks very much like a mirror image, right?
And so this could be even yourself like increasing your own personal power
And it could be significant like that looking in a mirror to and then the wands of course, you know
Wands are you know these magical tools whatever so so I don't know if you're if you're into that kind of thing
But yeah, this looks like
Yeah, maybe dealing with your shadow side or something like that, but I don't know if this is I'm even doing that recent past because
you're in some kind of like
Five of Wands is like a chaos, like a kind of, like a fighting, sometimes it's good nature fighting, arguing, you know, like it's fun, sometimes it's like, it's more serious, but I think that's like, you're pretty good natured with it.
Also, like there's a lot hidden that you will still be revealed to you, like you're really not supposed to know now.
I don't know if you've been through like some kind of some kind of sadness, but there's a message about like not like
Don't disregard the happiness you have for like if you even if you lose something like you it's like you're not gonna lose
You wouldn't it's not everything. Okay, so it's and it's like you can always fill your cups again
But there may be some kind of regret over something. I'm not sure
But that's about but I think with the moon coming up. It's kind of like it doesn't like that like that
It means kind of like you're not supposed to I'm not supposed to poke around too much in it
There's something hidden or some kind of
Information that you're supposed to find out later
But I hope that did help you. Okay anybody else and you can come on the panel to you and
Of course if you'd like to do a more detailed reading
You can donate and then I'll pull more cards for you also for members will get more cards as well. Oh
Hey CFC it's been a while. Oh, no problem. I hope you liked it
Oh, CMC, I'll remod you.
It's just I had, hey, Ron, oh yeah, I'll remod you.
I just have to like, let me see.
I have to, I'm just gonna have to make you a regular,
regular mod, it's like, I'm constantly modding and remodding
because somebody was deleting my band words list.
My only managing moderators can mess with the list.
Oh, thank you Katrina. Thank you. I look good. Thank you. I feel like I'm uh, I'm uh
I'm doing okay. I'm doing okay
Let's see. What is tomorrow? It's tomorrow's the 24th. Oh, it's tomorrow's Monday the 21st. Okay. That's cool
Can you drop jamie's link jamie? Yes. Can you give a reading shirt Katrina?
Of course, I'll always do it. What do you want to do alien tech? Do I have a cat deck? I have a van go deck
I have a rainbow deck
monster's deck and the cat deck which is the alien of course which we want to do
like out of that Katrina you like the monsters okay the monsters the monsters
the back of these cards. Yeah, this is pretty cool. These are just some good
checks. I got these decks on Timu and they're very much discounted. I think
that they are maybe, maybe reprints. Oh, this one just pops up. Okay. Okay. Okay, got
They had they don't come with it. They don't come with any books or anything. You just come to the very no frills, but it is yeah, it's good
In the fairytale
Oh, you like the fairytale. Oh, okay. Okay
Yeah
Castle of the Panic Ground of the Panicles.
Okay, claws are gonna be sore. Okay, okay.
That's what I'm like, cat. Okay, let me get word of advice. Okay. Okay.
Let me see. Well, it looks like you've got your reading justice for something, and I don't, and it was like this.
something that has really kept you up at night or something like that like
something that's really really when you sleep it's kind of like it's keeping
you up like you kind of have the sleep mask on right there right but that is
queen of the crypts right she queen of crypts which I would assume would be
the pentacles right it's like and so this is the I believe that would be you
Are getting justice
But I think they've been worrying about this for a while
And but you're gonna be getting news about this because we have like this night
Coming up you hope so. Yeah, you there's some news about this
I'm gonna come bring you something some good news or something or some kind of help this guy. He's very helpful
Okay, let me see one more
In the moon. Yeah, there's still stuff to be revealed, you know when the moon comes up
it's like there's like some maybe some illusion at work and just get to wait
for it to cycle go through the cycle okay so I hope you enjoyed that yeah guys
well so yeah yesterday I bought a lot bagel and locks and then I like left it
out and I hardly any of it and I think I might like kind of bake some of that but
Oh, I don't know. Do I want a coffee? I'm trying to... I'm... I'm hungry for something.
Let me see. Yeah, I just had to order these new cords. I have a lot of expenses.
My neighbors are still going to fix my bike. I think I just talked for the day. She's like, I should eat. Yeah, I will.
Uh, I have the locks. I'm gonna probably put that in the oven a little bit.
Bish Chocos, yeah. Oh, probably too late for them now.
Shit. Well, actually, they have restaurants to have them, but I think the pier is closed.
What time is it? Oh, it's Sunday. Yeah.
And they don't have happy hour on Sunday, I can't even remember.
I love how good it's Bish Chocos.
Yeah, so...
Yeah, I'm probably gonna
How many cars how many is the most cars you can pull for someone you can actually like you can we can
You can use as many cards, but how many would I like to let me see I'll do I would do with it one two three four five six
I probably do like
Maybe like ten that I would then I would maybe use a few different decks, you know
And so it's like I don't like I don't know when a reading gets to a reading gets too many cards
It can get convoluted unless you're like unless you're like using cards as the clarifiers of another card and stuff like that
and so it can get me because
but we do go through all the cards in our life right at different times and there's
archetypes and so the archetypes will very much apply especially in
as if I'm an art let me see if I can find an archetype here let me see
well the I mean the major archetypes would be you know the major arcana
kind of like half the deck like the emperor so the emperor is like you know the emperor is
very much like the drop like you like the vampire like the classical vampire right
you can very much associate an emperor with that kind of energy oh who got the membership by the way
Yeah, we have good fish talkers, right? It's the biggest fish market in California. I think
I'll post as many as you want. I mean, it's like I'll I mean, I pulled I pulled a lot of a lot of I
I'll do an hour reading with people. I've done it like a private reading
You do this over the phone some people who just want private memberships job Chanel. Oh great
Yeah
So, yeah, I'm really cool, really cool to be a,
there's guys, I'm gonna put like everything pretty much
on members only, like I'm gonna like take everything
off of publics, but I'm gonna put most of the stuff
on members only, I think, you know?
And so, you know, there's already over 100 videos there.
Like if you're so, if you'd like to watch the,
some people like to listen back to me,
but, you know,
I,
Have to keep them up. I don't know. It's a good deal if you like Benny try them together. You can't remember if you still like them
Yeah, I haven't I've been I didn't watch they're at a convention right now. I watched it last year
It was like so much fun last year. I'm just too busy this year
But Benny was just on the show. Did you see Benny was he was just on the show
Do you have a most most cars pulled
I mean, uh, no, I mean, it's all put all pulled up. I'll like just go with this many is like it will
it's usually like
For a basic reading like what I've been doing here is like I'm doing a fork fork cards for free
Like I've been doing like and it's kind of like past and current energies and then it's like an advice, you know, uh
Yeah, that's your yeah, that's your was fun with Benny. Yeah, he was just on the show for like about an over an hour
Yeah
Like someone that you just kept pulling cards. Well, you can't I mean, I think there's okay
So there's a Twilight Zone with William Shatner. It's all Twilight Zone and he goes to this diner with his girlfriend and
He like there's like a little machine at the dining put a quarter in and then it comes out little little fortune and it says
They should pull it out and it would say it said would say the guy over there
It's about to fall down or something and then we could look at the guy would fall down
And then all of a sudden the everything of the machine you would say was coming true. It's had the cafe
But then he started getting hyper
fixated on
Finding out the fortune it's always like there's certain so that's why I don't get into fortune telly and stuff
I don't know. It's a good question. I'm really I really appreciate you asking these kind of questions, right?
Yeah, so it's interesting I love talking about tarot and hey could yeah
Hit those likes. Thank you so much. Yeah, I mean doing I think I was doing a little bit better on likes last night than I have been
So I think people have been enjoying
Panels and stuff, you know, it's like of course like so that yeah, so Q named his show. It was called
Charging money day. Oh pay me money to hang out with me like and I could I know that he's think he's like
He's talking about me and then somebody's like
Who are you talking about? He's like, if you don't know him talk about you don't know anything
So I guess I'm like a hot talk. Oh, thank you money
Okay, like a card. Let's see. I'm pulling you from another deck. Hold on
No problem. Thank you. I'll put a few cards actually. Okay, but
Yeah, and so then he started he was just yet yelling and he's like he's like he's like hey
How about you pay you every time you stutter and he's like
Like I was like, I don't even know why I stutter really but maybe I do I'll pull from the van go deck
So anyway, he's like this salty, right? I mean, it's like why are we but I don't know why he
Why is he so mad about everything? It's like why am I still concerned with what I do? It's like
Jealousy jealousy jealousy it's such an evil thing. Oh, yeah, you do get remodeled. Okay. I'm sorry
I just haven't been on that. I'm not really posting. Oh, I will post my link again though
Let's take a second my phone's a little bit
Yeah, I
Mean why is he so mad
It's like
We're all on the internet. We all can like start a business. We can like do different things
We can like you know
We can if people don't have a successful YouTube channel or it's not as accessible as they want or it's like first of all
There's a few things you can do you can like
You know have an interesting show you can you know you can you can
You know have the panels you can you can go you can go to other panels and they talk to people and I meet people and say
I have a panel you're welcome
I've come to my panel anytime there's a lot of people that that really wanted like just hear themselves talk and we'll go to your panel
like right we've seen some of them on my show and
So there's people that just go to panels right and so it's like you have to put open panel in your
Title maybe that's what I was I did for like every day right and so they can find that you know
You do open panels when they search you'll get a lot of people off and so it's like it's like
and then you just do it all the time right the guy do it all the time and so I have a presence and
right so yes I'm sorry money for 20 I'll get right to you I just want to make sure I uh
so anyway I was wondering about like making money on tiktok too because Emma was on it
with like 23,000 subscribers or whatever right and uh she got kicked off but uh I was wondering so
Getting this one kind of program and then it's like a 10,000 you can get monetized, right? And I was like, what's strike one?
Oh, you're not that high. I didn't know I
Didn't skip. I'm not I'm honey. I'm not skipping your reading. I'm just I'm
I'm trying to I was like my phone is a growing really slow. I'm so sorry. Oh, my Wi-Fi is not on
I must probably went through all my data already
Anyway money for 20 what I got for you king of pentacles. Okay, you're really coming into your money
That looks like you know, this is a pretty good looking king of pentacles, too
Very you know, I'd say bless abundant your ideas are coming to fruition. This is just all it's all good things
It's also in your power. You're not really having to go and like try so hard
It's like things are coming to you. Have you noticed that at all seems like you're in that power, okay?
Oh, Queen of Pentacles. Wow. And this is like, you know, this is crazy. Okay. So do you have your soulmate yet?
I think it will be maybe another maybe another maybe a earth sign and
Somebody Queen I keep this is like a really power couple. You know this woman yet because it's like
Yeah, I see you two together. You know, I know
Maybe they don't exactly like you but yes, he'll be able to kill the coins
It's like abundance and she's bringing him some looks like or she's like she's like she's like bringing him some right?
And he has a lot of coins, right?
But they're both, you know, they're wealthy, right?
OK, there might be something set in.
So I don't know if you're with this person, OK?
I see this cut.
Oh, I'm sorry.
The others are not that bad, but yeah,
I was gonna say about the tower.
You know, when a tower comes up,
you know, a tower is always gonna be something like shocking.
I don't know, this tower,
this tower looks like it's pretty still upright.
You know, it's like, you know,
sometimes the towers are like, you know,
being hit by lightning or something.
This tower looks okay.
So maybe it's just some kind of tower, but.
But.
It looks like for a word of advice or the, I would say,
it's like, keep working.
It's like, you're almost ready to harvest.
You've been working really hard on something.
It's like, you're about to see the results
almost time to harvest.
I came back, yep.
There you go.
You can like, I mean, it's like,
you've been working really hard about something.
It's gonna pay off.
Okay.
Hi, babe. You wanna see Lunore, guys? Have you seen Lunore for a little while? Hey.
Want some catnip, Lunore? Here. Okay. Lunore.
What are you doing?
Hi.
Hi, George.
Give us some good energy
Thank you very much for you know, I mean
Pull you in these cacti
Testing
Yes, you ready? That was made the audio settings of the first show
Oh, that's why it's I'm not on my fucking tablet. That's why they're not working
Do you hear me? Okay? Okay, you hear me? Okay. Hi guys. We're going to say anything
See that's a little bit better
There's no you know what you want streamer needs is filters. What's up, Dottie? How are you see me? I need filters because it's like
They have some filters on another site called prism. Good to see you, Gaudi
Yeah, I'm thinking about getting some copies or something like that like I want to go anywhere
Um, I
picked in
Waiting for some stuff to come in the mail. I'm getting my job. I'm getting my my Jeffrey Dahmer glasses today
We're coming I think we should be here in a minute now, so it'd be exciting
I think I got a good one. I got the the van Gogh deck. Yeah, like
And it's like all
It's very um in that in that style like just out of this world
Great world
Yeah, so i'm returning these um and i'm just like because it's like
Very expensive. I mean, I got the night, of course, absolutely
Yeah, I mean, I got I like the nice
The nice glasses, you know
I mean, they're not even that nice. It's just like for readers. I don't they sell like, you know, 20 for
20 for like $10
It's like one part, please.
Oh, look, you got a knight.
That's a really cool knight, too.
This is very much like almost like a knight's Templar
or something like that, knight of swords.
This is someone bringing some truth and justice.
I think that pretty much fits in with you
and there's that solar heart, right?
big sun behind it so it's very a lot of a lot of powerful sun energy
especially in the season of Leo but but uh yeah yeah and it is like you know the sun
is related to fire but it's also related to the air also because yeah you like that card perfect
card okay great hope you enjoy okay just keep doing keep doing you
Whoa
Okay, so what should I eat though?
Now I can't like
You're in a deck. Yeah. Yeah, this this one was like I just like the I got it up to you
But yeah, I would say it's probably yeah, probably has a little bit of a nicer version available
Yeah, I was like, I need to try it out too. Let me see. I think I'll 17 bucks.
Yeah, I've got.
Stan. $17 not being like over $20 for this thing.
It's a fucking piece of metal with a
freaking
hole
Actually, I don't need a big one. I don't know all the same price
I think 17 dollars best I gonna do okay, let's do it
17s are good number anyway
5% coupon
Or I can get, oh, I can get a stand and it's having it on my desk.
Is that working better? Then it's only eight dollars sold. Always done the same. I'll see
how it works. I don't know. It's like, I have a table right here. I can just have a small thing
and like it'll probably be the same. I don't know. I'll get it figured out. Maybe I need to, I want to
I like this one. This is this phone stand also has a light on it. I can put this light on it.
Yeah, so what is it Sunday? Happy Sunday, everybody. Hopefully you're having a nice day. You'll see it on Amazon
It might be out of print, you know, like I've also I've seen like I was looking for the golden girls deck without a print
Nice you or it might be like a limited and see I'll see if I can see it
Like, I'll see it. Maybe they might have the real one too. Like they have, I mean, this is,
it might just be, it might be a reprint. Okay, so it says,
I mean, yeah, they have several decks.
I think they might have a real one, or this is one.
No import charges.
Let me see.
I think it's just, I mean, it's like,
it looks like the same one I have, you know,
but there's one local, which means you'll get like one.
a few days but uh they have a lot of different prices but it's between six and ten dollars.
Oh they have like, hold on, what is this one?
Yeah but I would recommend going maybe on um on Tmoo if you're rich this is in tarot or you just
I'm gonna try some next decks, go try Montimou, especially like, you know, but I would say get a Ryder deck for sure
There's there's some Ryder decks that there's a few dollars. And so it's like then you can just
You know, they're pretty good quality decks
They're these these are shuffle really nice. They're the same size if you're really good in the hands
It's just like the only thing is it doesn't have you don't have the
Nor is it made in China?
so
I just like, you know, oh, I hope they're approved by the author, you know
You love the new emojis. Oh good that that that one is my tattoo. You see the little um, the little black cat face
That's my tattoo because you
Yeah, you like the grandma one that one says grandma
Oh, what happened?
You said something happened with Seckie.
Is there a robe or a jacket?
It's like a P coat.
Sorry.
It's a P coat.
It had like a little bit of cat hair on it.
It's kind of like, you know, notorious for cat hair.
I'm sorry, I can't really see the comments too easily.
It's a little bit small.
Hi guys.
Yep. Oh, do I have duct tape? Yeah, I have duct tape, but it doesn't work. I mean, it didn't work. Look
It's like I tried
I did kind of yesterday, I don't know. Do you think like it's just like too, uh, it's too, it's too janky right now for that
Okay, so there we go.
So my Jeffrey Dahmer glasses should be here any moment.
I can not wait.
I'm gonna return these ones.
You like the eyes?
Let me see if I can, yeah.
I'm gonna say that's the one,
because then it's like, okay, so if I use this phone,
okay, this is charging, it's not even charging.
Oh my gosh, that's such a mess, okay.
I don't know, I,
I'll try, I'll try to broadcast with the Kindle, which I've never done.
Kindle is a little bit like, you know, they're inexpensive. They're very, so that's good.
But it's like, Amazon really should have opened it up to.
The Android, it uses the Android, the interface or kind of uses the kind of the Android platform, but it doesn't. It's not compatible with the play store and stuff. So.
Here we go. So.
Hello. Oh, you see me? Okay. How's that?
Okay
It's like so small it can barely read the comments in this one too.
Okay no worries. Hey Jan, how are you? And so thank you Katrina for donating the membership.
But I wanted to give back, of course,
like I like to do.
And it's exciting when people get a membership.
So.
My god, it's taking weird noises my phone is home
Oh my god, it's taking weird noises my phone is home
Dear Lord
Okay.
There was 238 views and like 14 likes.
I mean, there's nobody like like shows in it,
but like that is like, nobody likes it, like it's crazy.
Okay.
This kind of fits on here
And it does wow that works. Oh my gosh
Okay
The fuck how about let's make it a special night
Beep Beep received a membership and
Texas Cat received a membership and Hanadi Jaradot received a membership
Congratulations on receiving the memberships
Anybody want to help me make it rain?
Jimmy Jeth receives a membership. Oh my goodness. I love
Trying again. I don't know if I was like something fuck
The Wendy oh Wendy pack received a membership. That's awesome when you from Howard Stern received a membership. That's funny
Does this kind of balance on that? Okay
So well, that's pretty cool guys, I mean, I hope Wendy will come and say hi
But yeah, and it's also you know, but I will accept you know, if you if you purchase two memberships and then you and then
You you specify to me I would like to to be sponsored
Yeah, we're having some technical difficulties. I'm sorry
Yeah, I didn't mean to hey Jamie Rose. How are you?
Hopefully Jamie Rose you're not mad at me from the other night, right?
Remember you Jamie Rose got mad at me and she called me the n-word or something or she didn't call me it
But she said the n-word
Then I hung up on her
Uh, did everybody hear me okay too?
I don't keep going. It keeps like it keeps ending. Yeah, so I'm summer and Jamie
Jamie's Cowboys both sponsored on the panel for today, but they I'm waiting till either of them comes in once to start it because I want to make sure
So because I'm one wouldn't be
When I do this to start the panel and everything I'm gonna put I put their banner up
you know for the whole time the panel will go and so it turns it's like a
It's like it turns into a sponsorship. So it's a win-win. It's it's actually sponsoring the panel
So, I think it's a good idea.
Oh, there aren't pages. What's the point of what?
There's no sound? Is there sound?
You guys hear me?
Can you hear me?
Oh, Jamie said she's good. Good. Okay. Good
Yeah, good their sound okay good. Yeah, I
Hear you Tommy. I hear you Tommy. Can you hear me? Oh my god? This is so funny. Let's picture. Oh my god
Oh, yeah, well, you know, I have these
Those 8i photos up. I'm gonna start using them for thumbnails, too. Okay, so where's my my cords are out for delivery now
They're on their way
You can't hear me? Oh, I'll take it out of here.
Does this help?
This is a plastic wrapper, see?
Does that help? Is it louder?
Hello? Can you hear me?
Let's go to K.
Oh, shit.
Good that's better. Okay. Yeah, I know it's just it's in this little it's in this condom
So, I mean, yeah, I'm totally
Thirsty right now, so
I'm doing my freaking new glass. I'm so excited for my new glasses. They're gonna be so cool. I'm really excited for them
I didn't pin the link either
Yeah, so anyway on um, so take but tick talk what it seems to me is like
It's like a lot of like bots because it's just like it's all of a sudden
I have like thousands and thousands of like these women or but this like I don't know
They're like big it was like they just think they're bots and stuff like that and they're all saying the same thing
Oh, hello handsome and everything and it's like I'm like, okay
And it's, I mean, I just say trying to get the thousand followers so I can then get the first step of monetization
And then I get like the 10,000 and then I'll be able to I don't know how the monetization really works out
But I heard it's like can be lucrative for like some people. I'm not sure. Has anybody know anything about TikTok?
So
I'm fine okay
Okay, we'll be anyone that's come up what comes to come one-on-one. I'm fine. Okay. Oh shit
Okay, we'll be anyone that's come up what comes to come one-on-one. I'm fine. Okay
Okay, well, let's come one-on-one
Can I post it?
No, I'm fine, okay.
Yeah.
Hey, Twitter, TikTok got banned for good in September
and chart changing to M, is changing to M?
M is the number 13, right? 13 is better than the alphabet.
Thank you. I think I really love I think you did the me kissing Joe Shippley
Very very impressive AI AI
Art and stuff like that and you know, I can appreciate that. I know it's a lot. It is a lot of work people are like, oh
The AI does AI is awesome, right?
Making things like making like things really possible that were
Just not before, okay, so let me see, let me see you.
I would, but you tried playing with panelists,
like cats play with mice.
What does that mean?
Oh, Vanguard, oh, yeah, it's you.
Oh, yeah, well, you were a Vanguard, you were like,
you know, you're just very insulting to me.
And I mean, I don't know if you weren't trying to be,
but you were like, you know,
Very backhanded I felt and it was like I'm not dealing with it anymore
What up, man yo yo yo
There we go, hi, I just want to come up for a quick second man, I just want to apologize to you
And to some of your viewers, you know, when I came here, it wasn't with the attention
of bringing a lot of retarded people here that followed me here, you know, like Van
God and some of the others.
I was coming here just to troll you real quick and we were going to move on.
We ended up staying, you know, mainly me, I ended up staying here.
You know just hanging out with everybody and then all these fucking retarded people start following us over here like vanguard
Is it one of the main retarded people this guy? He's got some fucked up brain
We was already up here earlier today, right?
Yeah, he came up and he annoyed me within like five minutes.
And I just,
So you see for him for what he is just a fucked up brain
that just wants to fuck around.
Okay.
I just want to apologize for bringing them here.
I didn't bring them here.
They followed me here and they ended up fucking staying
and they ended up trolling you in the process.
I apologize for that.
Okay.
I'm just, it's just good training for me.
You know, I got a really like,
Be able to like, you know fortified one of like he's one of like maybe 10 to 15 that you're gonna counter. So
So much rain 15 15
Sorry, man, I'll make it up to you later. I'm sorry. I'll see you later
Yeah, before I bring bang our arm, but I'm gonna take the troll sign before
Oh, Sam, I'll bring him on.
Gotti, you brung the weirdos because you are a weirdo.
You hang with JT and the rest of them niggas.
Gotti, you a weirdo.
You brung the weirdos because you are a weirdo.
Never forget.
JT is the weirdo.
Rain's the weirdo.
Liggi is the other weirdo.
You a weirdo yourself, Gotti.
Who the fuck are you?
You a weirdo yourself, you don't fuck.
Nigga you a weirdo you broke the JT weirdos and fucking LD 15 never forget y'all to chill with LD 15
Y'all chill with LD 15 weirdo ass nigga. I'm out of here man. We'll see
Well, I mean, I don't know if he should be mod anymore
Just can't use the mod
No, and he didn't bring LD here. LD comes on his own and LD's LD's annoying
But it's like like I said, so it's like if people want to kick people off the show
It's like I'm hanging out. We're doing like trivia. I don't really cares. I mean, it's like it's not like anybody is like
Even if it's one's in prison, it's like they're not gonna they can't hurt you fucking, you know screen
I don't know. Maybe well, maybe they can I know
But maybe I'm too too too trusting or something, but
I don't know, I don't find him like, I just find him uninteresting, that's the thing, I think he's like, he's like, I think he has a ship on his shoulder, he's like, he just like looks at the camera mad, and now he's like trying, and he like, all these people that are so like, you know, so controversial, it's like, they try to like, they try to, they fucking end up like,
like, dang up on me, and it's like, I don't know, I don't know, I always like, would like, you know, try to like stand up for
People be devil's advocate and stuff like that, but it's like fuck. It's a very stankless job
Yeah
Here's a bit you're shaking smirk. Mmm. He's just sorry and it's like then he's like doing these stupid like Italian jokes
Like he's in the Mafia or something like that. It's like I mean it's like
You know we got he can get away with it. Not not fucking LV
Going to rock
So I'll play the Troll song
Saying wow shit flexing hate and fear, but I got glitter nails and a crystal sphere
Dug D talking like it's 1952 racist rants. Yeah, I banned you to view but every troll that clicks my stream
Just feeds the fire in this mystic queen
Trolls make the world go round but not in my space not on my crown they yell they cry they talk that smack
But I keep coming with the tarot pack
if Lucifer had a twitch they'd co-host the spot cute little demons with chaos in their eyes
but even they know not to cross these vibes then there's
Yeah
My kid this tabloid is really slow
Okay, I'm seeing a break
Yeah
That good
Yeah, well, I know but it's like
This story if you're the story like I got like I have like every full community here
Okay, he's backstage. Okay, Vanguard. Oh, okay. Well, but it okay, I'm gonna go. She's at she's Vanguard. Hello
It sounds like
Is in practice right here? Yeah
This is this is it's called a dictatorship. It's called the dictatorship of psyche where it's like I get to make the rules
And I get to enforce them and if you don't follow them, I'm going to
throw you into purgatory
Best or whatever, I don't know. That's where you do the best, which is just means that I'm blocked you from the chat
Um, I kind of like live in like kind of like a
Kind of a mishmash of heaven and hell. I don't know. It's cuz it's purgatory area kind of like nice big
Vacation not nice. Hey
It's my sequestrian. I'm a it's a good psychot. It's like a psychot. Let me see psychopsy copia
psychopsy copia
What are you crying God you don't cry
Yeah, watch this guys.
I'm sorry I couldn't hear you for the last 20 seconds, because you covered up your mic
there.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh.
Yeah, this is again, I'm using this other tablet and I'm not really used to it. So I'm trying my best
Right there. Yeah, um, what's this? Okay tell a joke right now
Right, do you want me to tell a joke? Yeah
Why do Americans drink Coca-Cola? Why?
Cuz they can't get seven up
Okay, who's backstage?
Um, you ready to get, huh?
Was that not funny for you?
I mean, maybe I'll have to, like, put him off to think about it in my mind a little bit.
Like, I don't really know what it meant.
Like, let me see, seven up.
Like, something like what?
Coke and seven up.
She couldn't get seven up, so she put Coke.
Can anyone explain it why did the why did the woman
Wait, Americans bring cool with cooler because they can't get seven up seven up. What does that mean?
Okay, um, well, I I'm gonna bump you for a better guess. Okay, bye
Hello psyche. Hi
How are you doing doing pretty good? How are you doing? Hey, do you want to hear a joke? Why do Americans drink coke?
I don't know. They probably want to get high on maybe they want to get high on coke
She couldn't get seven up. I don't know. I don't understand that you guys understand the joke
I don't I don't I don't get it. I don't think it's just like it may be some bridge since it's a little bit
Why everybody drink coke they might they maybe want to get high on coke
Yeah, but it's like bit. Okay. Okay. That's not I'm not talking my sniffing coke. They might want to drink it
Is they getting high on it?
Yeah, but it's like are they really getting hot? I mean, it's just sugar and I mean, okay
There's no man. I'm a caffeine. I'm a caffeine on you guys guys
He says the joke seems to be funny. I mean, it's funny. Not just for like you funny for everybody. So it's okay
It's okay. It's okay. You're like you alias. I bumped a guest for you
Yeah, I know
Yeah, you know that guy, um, this is a bandar
I don't I don't know him. I don't know really that much people on the arm you too
I don't even know the couple of people are out who I know from the other panels. Oh, you know, you're sure
You know, you know, you know, God, you're right. I
Don't know
You don't know
No, no, you know
There's no no a lot of people by their names, you know, I mean, I know they certain people
Okay, that makes sense
Like I know you from from Miguel's panel
From you right on the comments
Miguel's I wrote Miguel's yeah, that's how that's how I got the link when I got on your arm your panel
Well, okay, let me just
That was one time. It was late. No, um, I think Miguel want to sleep and
You was right in the common you say you was on open up a panel and then you put the link up and I just went on
Cool
Yeah, so let's see you don't want to know what
Means he means he I don't know what it means he heal on but it was everything
I mean, so basically, you know about my new panel rule, so basically, I've got two panels
scheduled.
They're basically whenever Jamie or Summer who purchased a panel spot yesterday, whenever
they say, oh, we'll start the open panel.
Yeah, I saw that yesterday.
You think it's a good idea or
No, they're good people, you know me
You know, they're not bad people, you know, they
Well, you know, I mean, I like them they cool with me, you know, I mean
Oh, yeah, no, I know I'm saying those things a nice person and some is a nice person. Yes. Absolutely. Absolutely
Well, I'll tell you who was who do not like it was cute. He's very upset. He's like
He put out his title of the stream
Oh, pay me money to talk to me.
And then he starts screaming about it in his chat.
And he just like, basically all he did
was stare at the camera on his show.
He stares at the camera for like 90% of the time.
And then he had Joe Shipley on for like a few minutes.
And then that was it.
I mean, it's like, no wonder.
I mean, it's like, that's your whole show?
You're sitting like you mean about me staring at the camera like like it's a good it's a loon and then talking to Joe
Shipley, you know to give me a good he ha or something like that about how smart you are or something like that
But but is it was the point and you're mad at me
For this just running like y'all say how can I say something?
Everybody everybody don't get mad about stupid stuff
You know I mean if you don't want to paint on mom to the person or you don't want to see they they you too
Whatever
It's fine. We'll treat you. I mean this you a person you're a human person and I don't know why a person will get mad
Right. I don't know. It's just like people just get though. No, some people are
are really really cool some people are just been like you know come up so yeah
come up money when it come up for 20 you open panels for free yeah well it's
like I am but I guess because I'm I'm running panels I was running open panels
with just like so many people coming in
And then it's like, there's a lot of personalities that are very strong.
It takes away from maybe being able to like do one-on-ones with people I'd like to talk to.
It's like people get a different personality.
Can I say something to you, Taki? Why you don't do an open panel?
And when you like certain people, you just charge them to come up.
And that's how you'll make your little money in your pocket for your panel.
If what?
You know, I mean people you mess with like the people who you talk who come to your panel a lot, right? Yeah going for free
You know, that's your friends. That's your
Like it's not a good idea comes like new people you don't know
Like the membership like for the membership or something like that
This is uh, this is just company. No, it's like that's not good business people
That's what people would get upset about when I started doing shit like that. That would be like
I was just thinking, I was just thinking, you know what I mean, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it, I'm not saying to do it
I'm just putting an idea.
That's all.
No, thank you.
I appreciate it.
But if I was to start to say, okay, well,
this person can come on, because I've known them this long,
or it's like, and it's like, then people will be like,
well, why did they get one?
They don't get one.
And it's like blah, blah, blah.
So it's like, it's really like,
if I was to play favoritism like that,
and then it's like, then having new people come in.
Oh, I got you.
I got to understand what you're saying.
But it's just like, you know, I kind of like,
And I like a one-on-one too. I do have the people on for free
Yesterday when we did the one-on-one with the um, I think Alice the girl
And I was listening I was listening on the conversation y'all was having yummy. I got all of this
I didn't want to um
Do my background so you know and fear when you're you know conversation
I just you know got off and I was just listening on YouTube
Right well, that's gonna mean it's good is but it's also good because it's like you know
It's good because we can come together and open panels occasionally and everyone talk and then it's like but then I get a chance to talk to people
One-on-one they can really get a lot of attention
Then I run basically the open panels at my pleasure
I was about to like just like stop doing them all together and I was like well
Either I'm gonna stop doing them or I'll just figure out a way to to make it like worth
So I would say this to you on psyche you got two people you got two good people who's helping you out
You know me. Oh, I have a lot. Yeah, I have a lot of people great people
No, you know a lot of people but I know that the only two people I know is on summit and Christine. I mean, oh, yeah
A lot of people are really like looking out for the stand like a lot of the agency of a lot of people helping me in ways that
So even if you're just here talking and not, and like, not seeing you.
Christine, Christine, help me out with my panel.
Please stop.
Yeah, Christine, awesome.
You know what I mean?
Got you.
Not like what she did with yours, but, um, she helped me out like she came on my panel
and she was talking to me and, you know what I mean?
Okay, come on.
Please stop.
What's going on?
Give this to me hard.
She's a very, uh...
I love nurses, I love golf lovers, I love animal lovers.
Yeah, she's a real nice person.
Yeah, I love people with good hearts, you know?
She gave me advices when I was downed out and everything.
She looked out for me.
Yeah.
She's a true friend.
It's like, you know, guys, if you do find true friends,
you know what, just hang on to them because they're not
going to be like that many.
People a lot of people. Yeah
Sometimes sometimes you can't um trust people, but um you mean a lot of good people in the world
But certain certain people you can't you know meet you meet them and they did backstab you know, I mean
Right, like I knew Christine for a minute. I knew some of them and I felt a lot a long time
But I knew them from from Pamela's, you know me and she's a nice person. They both nice person
They give me that truck. They give me the tough love
Yeah, and that's good and that's good sometimes and it's like and it's like it's like people like
Some people even if it's like tough love
They they need that it's like it's like as long as love, you know, it's like some people just hate, you know
And it's like so even if it's like tough love, you know, I appreciate that it's delivered with the spirit of love
They can anything, you know, I
heard from them, but it's like in there's a lot of people that are gonna be very
Harsh and judgmental, and it's usually the people that are like
Least to least qualified or like, you know
Most things will always point to fear other people and like, you know
Your friends with Alex just you need to use me. So
Alex on the show yesterday, you know that
Yeah, I was in the show for about a couple hours yesterday. She was real
Um, she's real nice. It was just really strange. It was really just random. I should talk about the little cartoon character that the girl was dancing.
No, Alexandra, her name is Alexandra Myers, I think, or something like that.
I was just looking at the on panel where everybody was talking and I see the little cartoon character dancing and stuff.
That was funny, you know what I mean?
Oh, that's a DJ Electra. That's a DJ Electra for sure.
Oh, alright, cool.
Yeah, it was a middle of stream. Yeah, it was good. It was good and she and she also she's a very nice little like no last night
I really want to
It's just Jesus. Thanks. Thanks me for having on the show and just really kind
Kind yes, and I hope look forward to me here. We had the same birthday. It turns out well
Not things that a couple years apart two years exactly apart born so it feels like there's not
It feels like this whole time, it's not, it's your face.
Well, I think it's your face.
My brother-in-law is my mansion, right?
And but, you know, he's my former brother-in-law,
so I'm not mad at the British, I don't know.
British people are fine.
I like the sense of humor.
It's a little bit dry for me,
a little bit sea sarcastic for me,
not really into Harry Potter and stuff like that,
but it's amazing, it's an amazing country, right?
I got out this you but you thought this out. What are you talking about? Oh, yeah, don't say that again, or I'm gonna I'm gonna ban you forever
Alex Alex has no Alex Alex is like the fucking
The insane person standing out of outside the police station with a picket sign or something like that
No, it's like walk on police station. We're talking about
I mean, I'm not gonna, Alex, Alex is like,
he's just, I'm just making a metaphor.
It's like, for this show, he thinks he like owns the show,
but he's just like this crazy person
that's like in the periphery of it right now.
You told him, you told him, NYPD, Alex?
Yeah, now it's NYPD, yeah.
Oh, he's a person, he's a nice person.
I know he is.
I have been back to you, but that's how he is, you know, I know
I've talked to him for hours and hours and hours and hours and hours and hours
Only I would you mentioned she would like to view it. Um, yeah, um, I think it is on members only probably
But I can give her a
Think I can give her a I can make it unlisted and give her the unlisted link or all I can make in public too
I don't know. I just don't know if it was there might have been some stuff that I'm not gonna present sure that
Huh
Oh
No, that was that was my friend telling me by and stuff. Oh your friends talking to you
I mean I say
You know I was talking to you, but he was walking off and he was telling me by
It's okay. Yeah, you remember last time you had some people in the room, too
Like you know people roommates or friends or something
He was talking to me and he was going home and stuff he's a I'll talk to you later. Okay. No problem. No worries. No worries
You talking does I want to listen more what you were saying I mean, huh? Thank you
Yeah
No, I'm just I'm doing okay. I'm
I'm having a night. Oh, is it now or haven't you fourth?
You know, you know, it's crazy psyche. The pitch is like the
arm, the picture you posted. Yo, some some of the pictures
you posted and look like you and then when I looked at it,
I said, oh, shit, I said, hi. You know what I mean? That you
had you was like Rico, Rico Suarez, like you kind of
your hair combed up and and your your face was like all
shaped up like like you had a straight shave then and
shit. Yeah.
I said, no, and I had a zoom in on that. Oh shit. That is like he that was to clean up a little bit
I could I could look like that, you know, I have to you chatted that may be available on psyche members only. Okay. Thank you
Yeah, I hope that she wants to say I think it was a good appearance. She sounded she sounded great
Yeah, so let me see it. So it is pretty cool. Now we have like, you know, we have people backstage like wanting to come on
It kind of makes it a kind of more exciting like
I get to kind of choose like who's on instead of like everyone like yelling over me and stuff and like
You have to control your panel sometimes. Yeah, when you tell a person to stop stop cursing or saying that um
M-word whatever word you want them to stop you have to let them know like you have to put your foot down
And this will make it even better for like, you know the other guests too because of all the person that sponsors a panel
Obviously one panel like we'll be there
You know I'm saying like telling people like behave themselves and like we'll feel like kind of like an ownership of the panel a little bit
Which is good. Yeah, also. It's also I'm providing the advertisement for if they have a channel if they have a website if anything
Anything they want to promote or anything and so if you have things from promote at any time guys, you know, you can always
It says, you know, it will be on the banner for the whole time of the show.
I'll mention it several times, then I'll, you know.
Oh, it'll be on the episode forever.
Also guys, I noticed on Rumble,
like I started to, I got these notifications
that like, oh, Psyche Awakens is on Rumble.
And so there, I was like, what?
And I like, and because it wasn't mine,
it was because I was posting these full episodes of my show.
Yeah, so somebody is streaming my show to Rumble,
but it's okay.
It's like, it says, it's like,
one of many shows on this panel verse,
Rumble account that so I'm like I'm syndicated on them. I guess and so they date so I'm already on rumble
So I'll let I was let them do the rumble thing
You know, I'm not really mad
It's like it because you know, it's really good because I get all my episodes even the ones that I when I end and stuff like that
Those will be up there and stuff like that. So, you know
So the all the all the old episodes that I've like lost
For since when they started those are up now. So
Sounds like merkin members only tonight. What the fuck you're so waiting backstage, but I know but I'm talking to my friend
LES right now. So LES you said you're a white guy, right?
Or
Do you have like how many people are in your apartment right now?
I'm not I'm outside right now. Okay. I always hear these voices in the background like at the same time
Every time I come on I don't be upstairs. You know, I mean, I like I'll be outside a lot
Yeah, okay, I like to I like to walk around New York City. Oh
Yeah, are you the one that rides the bike around New York? No, that'd be two different person
Okay. Yes. I'm so I know who you talking about
Okay
Yeah, oh, yeah, you know about here. He was driving around New York while I drive right into like the under the fucking
Cross the bridges and stuff. Hey, you read those on the school. Yeah
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, okay, so cats will and end up with bomb according to the cats will end up add
lip balm according to the movie the book. What do you talk in vanguard? That's why it's
Yeah, whatever you're saying does not just that makes sense. Okay, it doesn't make dollars. It doesn't make sense
Okay, let's do a beta. So how do we play trivia?
How do we play it? We can play trivia
Just what we can play it on a sponsored open panel or someone can sponsor Tribune night
Oh, I mean, you know, I mean just do the trivia because someone can say I just want to do trivia for the you know
And they can we can like, you know, I think it would be an additional
Besides the sponsors if you want to like personalize it you can say oh just three hours of trivia or just three hours of this
I'm just like all right. I don't know if you want to people want to make requests and stuff like that
I suppose you can discuss it
Like I like to like to you know work with people
Yeah, so it's cool to have an archiver though. It feels like oh, hey, I kind of made it
It's kind of like, you know, I'm psyche. How long you've been doing on these panels. Well, you've been doing it a long time
It's January from January. Wow. Oh
Yeah, it is long, I mean, it's not a very long time
It's like um, and I but I've been doing my show since maybe about like
Okay, that's not maybe since like
September-October last year I started doing like just like little videos like I like you know little like you know
It's what tell me it's and stuff like that then I'm back like October remember December
I was doing just like it's like occasional live streams, and then
You know I had like hardly I think probably under a thousand
subscribers under like you know hardly any watch hours and then like in January I started doing open panels once I started
Doing open panels everything just started taking off like it started like
And then it went to monetization and then it's like the monetization things took off again a little bit
And so it's just been like, you know, right?
Yeah, I see a lot of people be going on your panels. That's that's on fire
Yeah, it's really cool
Actually, you know, I see a lot of people go on your panels and stuff and I see a lot of people commenters and on the common area
You know me and I said, oh sure
I might ask someone then and I finally actually you know me
Mm-hmm. I'm trying to do my I'm trying to do my own panel, but I'm I really don't got time to do my panel
I do got a panel, but I don't really do it at all. You know me. Yeah, well, it's like maybe four panels and that's it
Yeah, yeah, because I'm well stream yard. It's like free
I mean give me just like 20 hours a month of not pay for my stream yard
Yeah, I pay for my I just don't use it. You know, my sister sitting there
Well, then the man is like you really want to like, you know, you want to make sure you're you're getting the
You're getting that paid for out of like, you know your show it giving that's part of the thing
I think you think that that will help you monetize certain things you can do things like put your business on it
Like you've advertised for other people you can do like other things with your banners and the graphics and yeah
I'm somebody's helping with that. I'm trying I'm up my mic bring my panel back on
I'm trying my shit and my boys up me my shit up
When I'm about to finish hooking my shit up,
then I must start doing my shit.
But right now, I'm just working a lot, you know what I mean?
It's like, you know, it's like, yeah, you're right.
It's like, you have to like, because it is like,
to be successful at paneling, I think.
Like, you know, we see who like has successful panels,
like Vita and, you know, Samann and things like that.
They've been very successful.
It's very, very packed panels, like every time, right?
And it's like, that's,
It's because they are the topical they're on the topic. They're in the community. They're known in the community
Oh, they think they're and so it's like you have to go to like a lot of the other community
A lot of the other panels and stuff like that and yeah, I've been doing that. I've been going to different people panel
I've been going yours and
Some other people
I don't think I've ever heard you mentioned like
Promote your own show or anything like that which you should do because you should post it
You know because every time you come in the chat or to ask a mod to post it or I know where you should have
Yeah, but sometimes people don't like people promoting they stuff on the on on they panel and stuff
If you have it if you have it as your like tagline or something you're advertising the people's podcasts on my panel right now
Like I don't really like that, but I'm not gonna like you know, you're not in trouble for it, but
I mean, it's like you're are you are you affiliate with people's podcasts are you just on the channel?
I mean, I'm not being honest. They
Know but you ask me there's peace
Okay, you asked me this before if they um, I'm like on the panel
I go to if they ever talked about you. I never when I went on the panel
I never heard them talk about you. Okay. Well, I mean, that's it's okay if they do but I'm saying like
How about like you write a boy while you're here? You write
psyches if you just write my mic
You know, because you're you're gonna go around people's shadows with my tagline. It's like, I don't know if the people's podcast said
Every time I come on your panel on the chat, I write salute to the panel and I say, what up to you?
And I don't disrespect you because, you know, you give me respect like everybody else give me respect
There's certain people I don't have respect for and I disrespect them
But you like you you cool with me, you know, you don't disrespect me
You talk to me as you know as a normal person. Yeah
Yeah, well, I mean, I like to I get respect to everybody everybody panel I go on I get them the respect
But if the people I don't like disrespect me, I just expect them to back
I mean, it's a it take to the tango. You know, I mean, yeah
That's why trawling is around I guess
A lot of people trolls and a lot of people do do pole pump bomb pump, whatever they call it
You know, I mean that's some messed up stuff. You don't do that in nobody's panel, man
And somebody trying to make their panel, you know go up or that had people talk, you know, they should not pawn bomb
Nobody's panel. That's messed up
Yeah, I'm in the middle. I'm sorry. I'm sorry a couple times on your panel
They pawn bomb you and you had to delete that whole panel in front
for something, some idea, it was stupid.
Yeah, and it's like, but other things have happened,
like where I had to delete the panel too,
people are disrespectful in other ways.
And so that's why it's hard to like,
it is kind of risky doing panel sometimes
because you don't know what people are gonna do.
People sometimes will just take action.
You're right.
So, you know, I'm just like, I think this is working well for me now and it's like I'm able to, you know, I feel like I feel like I feel like I figure out a way to like keep make this like have the show work and like have me happy, audience happy, have everyone happy.
That's what I want to do.
And it is you a happy person. You know, I mean and you're a happy person. That's what I like about you
You're always happy you like talking to people, you know, I mean, and you always found reading their cards
Like you ask people you want me to read your cards. That's real nice. You do that to people for people. You know, I mean
No, well, you know, it's really weird. You know Canada dry
You heard that person his name is Canada dry or like Saskatchewan or something like that. Have you heard of that for me?
No, I never heard of that
Okay, he um
Sask was like a person that came to my show. I actually have I'm actually gonna chair
I'm actually gonna change guys. I'm gonna change my uh, the member little member logo
because that
That was like the last thing I have up that he made for me because all your psyche. I have to do a delivery
I'm gonna hop back on
And I'm not a so I don't want you hearing that like the wind when I'm driving on the school day
Appreciate that
Yeah, and so yeah, so what happened is like sask like he
Used to be on he was like so nice and he would like make the graphics and like you know the graphics were like pretty cool
Like but you know they weren't like perfect, but um, but yeah, I was happy to like you know and then
One time I think like someone had paid to gong him and then like and I gonged him
And then I like even brought him back up and then refunded the person and then like but and then he'd even come on and stuff like that
And so and then ever since then he's been like just to know just kind of weird and then like
He's been really annoying and stuff. And so then like last time he showed up and he was on the panel and everything
I was like, I was like, oh whatever all of them sit there and
Then Christine comes on she's like she's like oh, there's someone sitting in your piano right now
Who is just talking the worst most disgusting shit about you?
You've got you've ever heard in your life like that
He was saying it on this on the show on a show last night saying things about you and he was he apparently said like something like
I was eating my own vomit on my live or something like that or something just like some kind of disgusting
Just making up some kind of just disgusting associations trying, you know, just like something kind of thing
We just like people say oh my god, you know, it's like something when you hear things like that about people
You're like some people are like, oh my god, and they get else
You think you made it that's true, and they get all like yeah, it's just like it's a very cheap thing to do
Thanks. It's like saying when you know Janet ate her dog and stuff like that. It's just like stupid, right?
And only the dumbest people believe but yeah, but why is he saying that he's not they're saying that and saying it
There's other horrible things, right? So go fuck yourself. Canada dry
Stain Canada not ever fucking come here again, and then he's oh, then he started saying oh, well, he started promoting a
Tony Tony the conductor he started promoting him like oh come to his some chat and or look at his chat
So it's like yeah
It's all some kind of it's some kind of like a stupid dumb demon like I'm affecting some of these people
I mean, it's just a ridiculous feeling and now
It's a demon of completely
It's a it's a I think it's how the
It's like a demon of smugness. It's where you think you just know everything
You're like the best person in the world and you're like you're God on the god and everyone should kiss your feet
That's basically the attitude he gives up
Yo easy
Not bad, how are you doing today?
Good
How's everything man? I haven't been on your pen. I've been watching for a while. What's up?
Not too much, like I'm a good, I mean it's been going good.
I started to, you know, start having the open panels
be sponsored and then just having everybody else
just do one at a time so I can do like a readings
one at a time with people or just like chat
one at a time with people.
And then when people want to like do a panel
it can be sponsored and it's like,
and then everybody can be like, you know,
have a fun panel that it's like it was getting to be too
many, too much, too much panels for me.
I stopped it last night, I came in, I got home and.
Started using the Wi-Fi stuff like that. I want to save my data. So I've been tuning in
So I jumped in on Wi-Fi and I saw was titties everywhere. I was like, damn
It was pretty crazy last night. I know you got a little more wild last night, you know, and we had
There are some, there are some, there are some milkers on display on this kind of.
I just say like that.
Yeah, I tuned it like here and there, but I've been right.
I'll write, I'll be like, hello everybody in this 93rd.
But then I, you know, I support other, a lot of other pages, so I gotta, I gotta support.
Yeah, I appreciate you being here and everything. Let me see. Yeah, I'm gonna get a bunch of refunds for some of this stuff
Like I'm about this gorilla like masking tape to tie up my like this tripod. It doesn't work
It's so did it break did the new one break?
No, it's I mean it's a tripod and so the new ones fine
That's but that only carries my cell phone and so the one I use my tablet like it like does not screw
No, the we know how it screws in and that's all worn away like you know, you know my screws get like
Probably say when screws good. Oh, we need it. We need it. We need a tablet a tablet scream. What size is that scream?
A phone holder for the time I've had me but I've been I now I ordered something that will just sit on the table because it's like
I said that I'm not like I got the kickstand. I got the kickstand now
Yeah, it's like it's kind of a less expensive one. Yeah, but it's like more of a guy
It's I'll have the perfect angle on it and stuff. It's just in right here. I'll say it's like all right. All right. All right
Because I know you bought one over Amazon recently, so I don't know if you'd like that would have a kickstand
Usually now that would see like that. That's just like it'll just sit on the table and like sit up like that. I think
Yeah, I think that'll be good
It should it should work and so you saw my you saw that thing here. They are my gorgeous alien
See him a little friend
Hey, Jamie. Well, whenever Jamie wants to I'm Jamie
I just read your little comic comment on the screen. I wasn't in the comments
Chris Jamie whenever you'd like to redeem your panel. I can start it
But just tell me what you want on the banner for your
You get shout-outs advertisements whatever you want to put on the banner you can just tell me what you want on the banner
I'll put it on for you. Well, I'll see you in the main chat. I see you in the main chat
I don't know my chat like if I see you regular
Oh charisma charisma. Okay. I see what you're talking about charisma been made a mod
Is that if you don't know psyches charisma
With me she made a video of you with the legs up and all that that's charisma. Oh
Rizani made that. Oh my god
That's it. That's her. Yeah, she comes in on a thousand names on thousand names. She got a thousand names
You got more than an Alexandra
Okay, well let me check
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you got to watch out with you got to watch out who you might good
Actually, but do you know this person or you know, you got to really know who that person is
Yeah, I think I got really drunk one night. I was modding everybody
Okay, I'm happy you didn't mommy don't mommy. I don't want to be mod
Because all I do is look at pages when I'm odd and block when you tell me to other than that
I don't I don't block nobody
I don't block the comment
Let's see. Let me check one second
Charisma just wrote. I believe Charisma just wrote
She's a drama queen
Well, I mean, it's like it's just it's just like a little bit con. I mean, it's okay
I mean, I don't really don't care that you posted me in the speedo. I mean that was public domain or whatever, but uh
It's probably
Probably better that you may remain a chatter but that I appreciate they have obsessed with me. I'm sorry. I'm sorry about that
Now I'm starting to read the chat I don't want to read the chat
I try to stay within the check the last time I read the chat and I got caught up I caught up with the chat. So
Yeah
Let's see
Yeah, I get to block people. I don't like that's why I don't want to be modded
I get to block everybody. I don't like it and when I'm on it it will block them that blocks the whole thing and I
Don't want to be blamed for something, you know that I personally wanted to do. Oh
Shit, I never remodeled the CMC. I'm sorry CMC if CMC Zara CMC asked me and I kept it for giving
Okay, I think I have all
I think everybody's okay pretty much.
Okay, okay, fix the, oh, sure.
Yeah, yeah, so the last night was fun.
Well, Atun did not the last minute.
Like good.
Yeah
Damn, this is I want to go up there. Matter of fact, no, I don't want to kill the vibes
Here we had summer Marcy Fox and
Damn, I'm like, damn, they don't have one even Chris cabs up here. We call them cabs because um camera action
Yeah, awesome, okay, well, it's okay, it's okay
There so there we go
Robert says mod me
I'm protected by Kremlin. I'm safe. Well, I haven't predicted by the Kremlin. Oh my gosh circle juggers
Hope you're having a wonderful day. Yes, Jamie
So Jamie, let me know when you want to open your panel because you get you I think you uh, you said it's what they said
You donated last night and so I want to thank you
Let's get some people up here man. Um, the links are on the top. Yeah, I already know what time it is
Yeah, we had some time right now
One at a time until until Jamie says we can open the panel or somebody else
I'm sorry about that. I didn't know about that. That's why I was I was waiting in the back for like 10 minutes
I'm like, okay. I gotta wait till he has to leave or something. Yeah. Yeah
I thought you was like I bet in problems for a second. I'm like, okay. So you don't want me up there right now
No, no, no, it's like it's just it's just one at a time because like I said the dopey panel is like gonna be like
Oh, she said, yeah, you pick, I believe.
Yeah, you pick, Psyche.
So if you want a couple people up, then it's on, you know,
act right, then make a decision together, you know?
As a community.
So Jamie, do you want to type, Jamie,
if you want to have like some text in the banner,
then I'm going to put, like, thank you, Jamie,
for sponsoring the show, hold on one second.
And then if you want to.
I don't understand what the sponsoring thing is.
Yeah, well, it's like though during the panel they sponsor whatever if they want to do on their channel name on there
Or if they want to like shout out or whatever they want to put on the banner they can have that and they're also immune from being kicked off
the show too
So it was all say right here. It says the panel is open. Thank you. I just
Thank you, Jamie. I will open the panel till 10 o'clock
Money I told you dumbass already money money for 20. I told you hit me up with your email and I will let you
Join my panel page or you have to control it
Cuz I'm money for 21 to save up for a new phone. So I'm trying to open I'm trying to help him save
So I'm giving access to my panel. I'm barely usually I use it like once a month twice a month
So yeah, I got the all access one to 80 something one. So I got you know, I've been burning money for no reason basically
Yeah, well, that's what money is for to be spent, you know
So hold on one second until 10 p.m. Thank you to you psyche. I see you growing if you need access and you can't pay for your
panel, do you let me know?
Thank you. I mean, I should be okay
I mean it's like because I actually paid like 25 bucks for StreamYard, which is like a discounted like for the next six months
And so I'm pretty good on it. So Jamie
Tell me how to do it. I already know you're not gonna be administrative. You're gonna be second in command
Pull a profile for you and that's that is a whole thing. I have marshy fox
I had some guys staying in the Stephen King cash run in new york
And you know, uh, and they were all when they couldn't handle when they couldn't pay the bills. I bless them
Nice, you're very generous.
I want to just put up to the announcement real quick.
Let me see, I think this will mean that the panel is open,
but I'll think of another sound effect,
but I do have a couple sound effects, let me see.
I think I'll just use like the fairy bells,
and then I'll let it run.
And then I'll put up to like the banner,
which says panel is now,
Open and find the overlay. Where is it? Here we go
And it was open hey guys
Well, not there anymore. Okay. Well, he was there the entire time until I open the panel
You need it you need a overlay this says shut the fuck up. Yeah
Jamie's that okay
So guys, yeah, the the panel is now open until 10 p.m
What's up? Yeah. Yes. Yeah time is three hours from now. Oh, it's 10 30 now. I'm on time 10 34
Check what? Oh, yeah, and then I think you want to link again
I guess I'll be
But I can do in guys I love to link his page
Maybe it's not
Yeah, money. I'm dead ass about that. I just read your comment. I'm dead ass. Yeah, that's what I used to do for people
They couldn't pay. I used to bless on the panel. I'm dead ass about that. You gotta ask them out. Ask them about me
Yo, Saki, you stuck you stuck like my my services getting low. I'm using data right now
How's it going
Say hello body. Oh
Body out let me stop let me stop before my wife pull up on me like Nick. I'm taking a plane
I'm playing take it right now. I'm gonna take a plane right now, and I'm gonna slap your ass when I get there
I'm getting you glasses funky. I'm in my Jeffrey Dahmer style glasses
You know what glasses I like, you know the um
They like circle, but they get they small they like compact or whether you should just put on your nose without without no extra
Shit, but then they put the action they put the one with the line that goes to your nose. I mean to your ears
Yep, I like those I like those the show like home was once
Thank you. Thank you for another panel. I don't know. I'll have that one after this one tonight
We have panels tonight guys, we're good see thank you so much Christine sponsor panel
Thank you
Yeah, guys, I think this was really really well. I think also people will be more like more better be hanging on
You titled his dream last night. Oh pay me to talk to me
And then he started screaming about me.
He didn't mention my name.
I say, I say, I call it now.
Arthur's going to be the first bitch about it.
She's like, you know, the thing is, I will still like do one on one call.
So also talk to Arthur like, I mean, it's like, it's like, I'll talk to Arthur one
on one with that.
It's like, that's free, but it's like everything about everything that makes
you money.
Remember that?
I know I observe anything that makes you money, anything that blesses you,
anything that makes you better.
Arthur bitch is about it.
Yeah
Well, I mean it's I just like I wanted to continue to like do my channel and stuff like that and it's like you know
There's gonna be like slow times and you know and stuff like that and I need to make sure I have like you know
And I'm just being smart with it and you know and even if it because demonetized
I'll be able to like continue to do this system and stuff like that right and so it's like a
It's my life. I know it's my way to be able to do this channel. And
You still got the block system you still got the now you got the sponsor
Another the safety from the block system, you know, it's like kind of like if you know
When they get out of control then they deserve it that's simple as that
Well, I think about it. Yeah, how are you?
That's the main thing about internet everybody want to come here and have fun even the trolls want to sit here and troll to have fun
Like everybody doesn't have fun
Ultimately, it's their entertainment, but it's like it's not a very like
You know predictive form of entertainment for me like it just it's like it grows off the vibe of the chat. It slows things down
It's like it is distracting. It's it's mean spirited
illegal things
Always like people but it's like people are mean and like
rule
Slander is
People in jacket feel like you talk too much about your channel and what's going on? Yeah
I know I kind of do but then that's kind of my personality too. It's like I want to share
There's only one person I go hard on and everybody knows who that is that's a dirty bitch
I'll put a picture up right now. I want everybody to fucking troll
No, okay, so easy we don't do that, you know, we're not doing that. Okay easy no
You know what why don't you know you don't put people's pictures up, okay? Don't put people's pictures up
Not sure what he's saying. Okay, but it's like I just thank you for not doing it before
just doing it but
Don't put up people's pictures and take control people think you can say baby
channel you can maybe say
But I don't even want that. Yeah, it's like I don't really don't want it like attacks
The big word was if this is what I say if for it if I do that you'll be a little bitch about it
You know I'm saying should be mad cuz she took all big yeah
Go to my page don't worry about it go to easy cameras on go look up a picture and go look up the last live
I did I dropped her picture and her daughter picture
She said her daughter was a minor five years ago. So
And she's selling
Okay, well, I don't know
I'm really careful. Okay. Yeah, I mean, I don't know but Ron's bird you can talk about what you want on your channel
I'll talk about what I went on my channel. Okay. Thank you. I respect your channel, bro
I know I know what to do and would not to say I follow you
Yeah, if I do that you be mad bitch
Well, he's a bronzer hates everyone he says and he's like drugs. I hate everyone like what's wrong with you run for?
Yes, I'm gonna sound like you need a psychiatric right now if you saying all that. Oh, thank you. Thank you
Oh, Jamie, that's so sweet of you. Yeah, cuz ghost wasn't gonna pay me back
Like it wasn't gonna be me up with then and I could put a kick them off
I said we're gonna get back on the show until he paid me because he was
Yo, psyche, yeah, I don't want to suspect your channel
I want to say something to this bozo ass nigga right here. Excuse my language. Sorry to say that
I'm a life-wrapping guy. Yo, well, what's your what's your problem with me, bro?
And shit, whenever that happened, remember what you said about me.
Remember what you said, just remember what you said.
Yo, right, it's me on the screen.
Remember what you said.
If I wanted to say something about you, I'll say it in your face, bro.
You can't say it.
Go back and watch it, bro.
I told you, bro, remember what you wrote.
Like I told you, bro, I've got no beef with you, but if you want to make it beef, we'll
bring it on, bro.
No, no.
Be a hoe.
I told you this already, bro.
Oh, guy.
You don't want beef with me, puppy.
Bro, you wanted it bro. What's up, bro? You wanted it bro. What's up?
You don't want that bro. You don't want that bro.
Remember what you said about me. I don't forget what everybody said about me.
What you wrote was the same.
What I said is what it is, what it is, bro.
What you wrote, what you said, exactly.
What you got a problem with it bro?
You got a problem with it.
You want to stand up? You show you don't want to crack a bone or something?
Yo bro, you don't want it, you don't want it.
You don't want it.
You know me
Skinny crack head nigga, I don't give a fuck
Like I told you bro, you know what the fuck it is.
Don't start.
You really look like a cracker.
You started it, bro.
You started it.
What's up?
Don't start.
You want to come or you want to go.
I told you the day.
I don't care about what you said about me, right?
Listen.
Listen and listen well, youngster.
All right?
I told you I don't care about what you said about me the other day.
If you want to keep people, we keep people.
You slipped over the picture.
So what?
I made funny you, bitch.
You got heart.
You got heart over that.
I really don't care.
Bro, I don't really care how I look, bro.
I don't care, bro.
That's all you do so pitch is up bro. That's all you do bro
That's all you do you hide now in Florida bro. You're not in New York, bro. Come on
Why you took that gangsta shit bro like come on
Why fuck with a crazy nigga
If I'm such a crazy motherfucker, why fuck with a crazy motherfucker, why bother hunt you down and do what I gotta do
Do what you have to do, bro, then what then what?
You want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to show you bro. What's up? You don't want to start it. You think I'm taller, bro
Don't matter
Whatever
You got people my nigga
That's nobody. How about that? I got nobody. Oh, I'm a one-man. Oh me nigga
I do what I got
Bro, and I rep my shit, bro
Come on, baby. Hashtag that motherfucker one man on the fuck out of here nigga. You know me
If I don't got beef with you, we'll leave it like that bro. Have you
Bro, if you want to be you don't bring it. Don't want it, bro. That's word. That's word in my pocket. Yeah, bro
But you don't know who you fucking with bro
I'm telling you bro like chill out job without you bullshit, and I keep it like that
Oh, you know I mean
The Peaboo's podcast who you working for
I feel like you're trying to believe me, what's up bro, I feel like you're trying to believe me, what's up bro, what's up bro, like I told you bro, anytime anything about it, I already know everything about you too
I'll go to meet up, bro.
You really mad about that?
Come on, man.
You talking, you talking, you talking, you talking,
you talking, you talking, you talking, you talking,
you talking, you talking, you talking,
Yeah
Y'all want to see less I'll make that my main profile pic anybody
Quick and see how you look
Cam up man
Yeah, what address bro
Come on money
You want me to get your address you have you got my address, bro
You don't come in that you want me to doctor. Are you are you testing my limits?
Bro, do you want?
Top of time. I'm all boy. Are you testing me? I'll doctor. I'll doctor my neck off
I'll doctor on my neck off keep playing with me. Say another fucking word
Shut the fuck up. Yo, it's over with
I got you, I'm a doctor, I'm a doctor, if I get it right, I might dox your apartment.
Bro, I don't live in New York, dox whatever you want to do bro, I got told you, like somebody
else tried to dox me, somebody else tried to dox me and they got the wrong information.
You know hi boy. We go see we go see
Your name is lower east side get the fuck with the block niggas go suck a dick pussy fuck out of you force claim
Oh, fuck my dick from the back
I got you bro. I got you say no more
Done. Yeah. Yeah
You're done
Don't resist
Oh, you don't do the same thing like you did to the to Eli you won't do the same
Don't do the same thing what you did to Eli to me. What's up? I'm scared bro. I'll tell you like this
I ain't scared of God, bitch. I'll tell you
I ain't trying to kill you. I ain't scared
I can't win them all
I'm not cocky
Well, you starting shit. You don't want bro. You started there
I'm you started it bro. I
Bro
When I had a panel the other day where you couldn't join
Want to go to your panel, I will never go to your panel, bro
Why you be shunned from that that name under your name right name on the alias
Ah, you shunned from there nigga, don't cut off my panel, you get shunned.
Yeah, yeah, I don't want to go to your panel.
I don't represent your shit.
They say to the new better you do better, nigga, you master to your slave, nigga.
Stop playing, bye-bye his laws.
Nigga, I don't represent the mother of God.
Don't go to your panel, nigga.
I don't represent the mother of God.
If you do, if you go over there, I'm not letting you on my page.
Nigga, I don't want to go to your page, you motherfucker.
exactly I got that recorded too nigga I remember that fuck that's all you say
that's all you do all you do is bully people that's all you do is bully people
that's how you do I'm a bully how how about bullying and I'm fucking
talking about me girls panel bro we're different page bro the fuck you
When was this you know when was it bro you use somebody panel somebody use the user name and you pump on Miguel's panel, bro
What proof you got on that cuz you know damn well that was cack gaga in the last last three four
Bombarding cack gaga and her mother. You heard that's evil. I in the chat right now
Keep it honest. You've been poor money and a lot of people. Yeah, come on. Keep it honest, bro
Who did I pop up nobody? Well, you're poor mom a lot of people
You know what I'm talking about bro artists you I think you're working for you working for I ain't working for nobody nigga
I don't work for nobody. Yeah, nigga. I don't work for nobody nigga
Yeah, you gotta be on her team
Your holy door, what up, baby? I think you're gonna say hi
Isaculations whoop
What proof you got if you don't got no proof then I hear nothing
I'll get the proof. I got you
Say no more. Go get the proof.
Say no more, bro.
Go to your store, get the proof.
Go get the accusations and all that shit.
Say no more.
I'm not that type of person.
I don't do porn bars, papa.
I'll curse you out.
I'll be like, fuck you in this damn dirt
and whatever the case might be.
But I don't do porn bars.
It's not in my resume.
Go check my record.
Fuck, wrong with you.
Don't fuck out of here. You think you want to talk so much shit, bro? Come on.
What shit am I talking?
Bro, we dead of the issue, bro.
Bro, we dead of the issue, and then you bring the shit up again.
Come on, let's make fun of your pictures. Oh, I don't care. Yo, bro. I even laughed about it, too
Like you mad cuz I made fun of your picture
Cuz I make fun of your picture you suck
Bitch click you on a fat dusty bitch click you on this nigga Eli's dick
People podcast you man
What the fuck is a people's podcast?
Man, you can't just have ever said the people's podcast.
Ain't no fucking people's podcast.
They don't fucking talk.
What the fuck is that?
Okay, gentlemen.
Time out.
LES. Easy.
Please listen.
I'm gonna say this once, and I hope you both listen.
Okay?
You both are good men.
You may not agree that both of you are good men.
LES?
They're gonna be people for or against easy
Boys gentlemen
Okay
We all have friends that are all together. We're friends with LES. We're friends with easy
There are some people they just can't talk because of the shit that goes that they put out there towards the other
Person, okay. It's both an LES. No, I adore you easy
No, I adore you. Can you two please when you're on panel just find a different commonality?
Please
He stopped fucking with me he stopped fucking with me. I'll leave this shit alone
I'm gonna leave you alone. Look, by the fact I'm with the leecher picture right now. How about that? Thank you?
I'm gonna beat your picture for that edit avatar section
I'm gonna take you over right now if it drops because sometimes it drops
Let me let me focus. Let me see if I could get it without we see the next
All right, look at yes, it says delete this avatar. I just clicked on it a little X in the corner. I'm gonna delete it right now
Delete it's gone
That's the only one I got deleted out of the fucking gallery
That be you happy I got is gone now you got to ask the person that got the live
They got it up there to take it down because other than that your face is up there
So I can't do nothing after that. I I officially believe you
Thank you
Yeah, I got uploaded it to the stream yard. I deleted out my gallery
We appreciate
And this is part of adult team is try to work it out and get a mom
And like I said, you're a good man, LES is a good man. I'm sure we can find some commonality
when we're on panel because we like being on panel and glad and less. I'm I'm happy to see you on the
panel. I'm excited that you're joining us. I like that one thank you. I told you I like that back there.
I'm good. I have to leave it there and I ain't I ain't pathing. I'm nothing. I okay, you know, your name's not alias be quiet
Yes, ma'am you look look look at the name. Look at the name you I
Just wanted to make sure that alias is and he's probably got he's probably busy with the background noise and I understand that
He's driving. He's got kids around he hangs outside. There's a lot of background noise
Oh, Jan, you know I don't dance. Get out of here.
No, I enjoy LES on panels, and I'm glad LES is coming to join us.
Right?
Thank you, Christine. Sorry about that. What you said? I just wanted to make sure you're okay, and I and I hope now I'm all right
But it's like what he said, you know what what's on he told me like a couple days ago, you know, you know
It'd be cool and then next minute. He did what he did. That's a fucked up shit
Okay, well
That'll happen on the same panel
I do understand that but you know you did that and I was laughing about it and then
Now when I go to your YouTube your YouTube panel and I see my picture on your fucking page, bro
You don't do that shit, bro. I will do it to you. You don't do that shit to me, bro
Simple as that
Yo, I'm the king of assholes. You don't know about that. I'm a mother. I already know you're
a king of assholes. You're a king of dickheads. Yeah. Okay. So, the weird thing is, I'm glad you're
joining us on panel. Okay. I stopped going on the panel because I had mad shit in my mind.
You know what I mean? I had mad shit and I still got mad shit and I got anger. A lot of anger.
And I really don't care. Like I said it.
I'm not scared to die, bro. I don't
We have a good group here and you know
Christine I thank you for being there for me when I was downed out. I think
But I will always be there for you. Yes when you need me to
That's why I always when I need somebody to talk to that's why I always come and hop on summer's panel and I'll talk to you
I mean to get a race
Right, I don't come on the panel to want to curse at people just I'm not really like that
I'm a nice person, but I'm
Just because I made that mistake don't get me twisted
Everybody does, everybody does, but anyway, I just want you both to know that a lot of
people enjoy the tour of you and I do like seeing LES coming over here also, so that
because he can get to know new people, you're going to have a comfort with the people you
already know, LES.
You got this, sweetheart.
No
But we can forget we could ask grown-ups we learned to forgive but we never forget about it you heard
Yeah, that's facts you're right
I'm going back to my granddaughter now. Yeah, I'll be safe. Thank you site for letting me in
Thank you, Christine. I may be back here my granddaughter goes to sleep, but for now I'm spending time with her
Why you got them biggest glasses off work? They look nice and pristine. I'm here for you
Yeah, were you at the bathroom I see towels
I am. I am. I am. I am. I am. I am. I am. I am. I am. I am. I am. I am. I am. I am.
I
Was your new glasses like
Looking sharp. Thank you
Yeah, I do less is coming the Jeffrey Dahmer style is coming out on the way. Oh, yeah. Well, maybe not
I'm gonna see him in the night club
Hmm. Hey, easy. What happened, ghost? Can you say, yeah?
Ghost about to crash out
Not tonight. My friends are on here tonight. I mean if you guys want me to crash out, I'll crash out for you
That'd be fine
Have you ever crashed out on yourself?
Oh, yeah. Well, there was the one time. Yes, I have yeah, you know
I you know actually now that if you guys want the honest truth
I crush on myself more than often because I play video games and I rage a little bit so I'll fucking crash out
You ever broke it. I don't throw my controller or nothing, but I don't throw my controller or nothing, but I do crash out
Oh, you never broke the TV then
Never broke TV. I broke a controller like way back in the day, but
Yeah, I'd be crashing on myself and I'll try to like debate myself. I'm like you fucking retard you went left
You should have went right, you know, I think it's the bait himself. That's crazy. You ever lost or you always win
No, I lose why else would I if I always win why would I debate myself if you always win? Why would you debate?
You're got to be got you're
On the battle on yourself. You and I have you really to say you heard right say you heard again
You're yeah, I'm saying you're you're
Dum-dum
What credit what the fuck is the psyche doing looking at fucking cornhub I came here to talk easy in sight
I got a bone to pick. Oh
You got a balance a pick
Bound to pick yard. We got a bone to pick. That's what's up. Oh
Yeah, I picked that bone
Well, psyche last night
After I left I pulled a card and
Guess what card I think?
Trickster trickster we need a panel card reading. Would you like me to pull another one?
and that's it. We need a panel reader. One panel reader, psyche. I'm going to mute up until you're done.
Hold on. Go ahead. Go ahead. You say what you're running. Okay. I'll do a reading for the panel.
Yeah. Trickster. I pulled it. I was like, psyche really? And then because all that shit happened
last night with the money and everything, I pulled a card and guess it was trickster card.
Well, the trickster
All the tricksters is a magician the trickster is a magician all of it all this is using like that
Yeah, but a magician
So a magician is a fraud
Create change right and so no no he's a fraud
No, no, no tricksters are known in like the the shamanic community to show you great truths about yourself and to
In to it in re-enlightenment. There's like many tricks or spirits and it's like they sometimes will be as
Sometimes they'll be misleading but
Word trickster has to do with like trick. You're tricking them into something. I was like a magician now
You're gonna say you just gonna be kicked off the show like you seriously
You're like a little one step. I don't like these big stuff like that being said about me
It's really slanderous. It's like that's the opposite of my intention or anything. I understand. I didn't say anything about you
I just said I pulled a card. I didn't say anything about you
You don't pull a car you don't have there's no card when you pull the car
Well, what deck do you have they pulled the trickster out? What what card is that?
Like I that's like usually not a typical card. You pull the card you put
Might be you got what do you got? Yeah, it's like he's right. I
Have the ultimate deck. He doesn't have a day. No, no, no, no, you got to believe me on my deck
I don't challenge you on your deck. No, you don't have a deck. I don't got a deck yet
I see I'm right, but then you didn't even walk on
Well, you know that did you ghost I mean you guys are just being ridiculous
How much I'm I ridiculous I was even trying to
With me with like what's the problem? That was a joke. I don't have a bone to pick dude
I had a bone to pick you'd know it
You know it sounds like a hairy
I wasn't I was talking to psyche. I said I pulled a card had nothing to do with you dumb dumb
Did you hear in my voice? Okay, what I haven't how do I have a problem with you in my go ahead?
Then why'd you open your mouth? We don't know
Well, that's good that that's a good one you're learning
Pull the work. You want to kick me off where I can just leave. I mean, I just
Want to out the chat was gold gone
Well, I sponsored it so they can't
You didn't sponsor you sponsored one two nights ago. She goes so your sponsorship was
Tonight is invalid access denied
It was like that's what it was like last night because last night was when you paid me but the first night was when I
I know I spy. I paid you last night to sponsor tonight's thing. No
You're gonna be more clear on the rules brother
Okay, that's a lot. It's the last time I give you ghosting credit for sure
Well, you four people talking at once. I don't fuck you got to be more clear
Okay, write that shit down and put it in the fucking description
I will I'm going to actually that would be a good idea actually
Say the banner says it but it's like that the banner's changed right now because we're in a sponsored panel right now
And we have two more to go tonight or one more to go maybe one tomorrow
I have two more in the everybody on the panel. Just give a shout out to JB Calvin real fast
Well, I'll give it an opportunity to have an open panel. Thank you
Child to you. What do you say?
Yeah, I should now you deaf and dumb
Jamie's Cal. Oh, well, I guess I am deaf. I didn't hear it. All right
All right, but you got sight you can see right or you talk with your eyes closed
Now you deaf dumb and blind literally
You could just repeat the name instead of being dumb
Jamie Cowboys about the sponsors this this segment of the shout out that Jamie Cowboys
And she also she was first trying to just cover for you ghost because she didn't think you were gonna pay
I know I know I know I was here the other night when they did that. She's a moderator. She has a rinse in her name
Yes
And she did throw that money, and I did it right behind her. I remember
I
Didn't disrespect it you heard
Okay, that's run it let's run it I didn't disrespect her so what are you trying to even talk about you always trying to argue
Let's run it what do you want to run?
That mouth because that you do it pretty good. Keep running it. I don't want to do the forest guns in a with you
I was just talking with you. I caused your reaction
job faster reacted
Yeah, because that's what we do
That's what you do yell out to the screen with you. We that's what we do just like I said
I was bone to pick with you and you're quick to jump on that
Listen here listen here with your New York accent. How can I help you? This is text message. Oh
Yeah, you sound like and then I got my camera like hey don't start it
We're in we have to deposit $10,000 into the finger. My friend the burden of proof is on you
10,000
Take out the cash listen if I don't have 10,000
But if you want my credit card information and my social security, I will give it to you right now
I need every information to make
this, I have to fix this problem you have.
All right.
My name is Syke, my social security number is.
Syke, you got scared there?
No.
I have a song to you. Um I have a song. I want to listen to your song. Your song sucks. I was on Summer Channel. They made a song for me. It was AI. No, you're sorry. It was very good. It was very good, but I don't join and ask you to play my song. I'm not Alex. You're. That's like me. It was funny at that moment.
Stop this.
Hmm.
Be rare.
Okay, that one.
Don't die. I can't figure it out. I'll have to look in the lyrics like we never released a whole album actually
I mean I have 12 songs right now. I'm gonna write but you gotta move back a little bit all I see is the beard
Yeah, I'll fix the style. Hold on
Yeah, I mean you put this down yeah, because
This is on a different tripod right now. Yeah, um, I really do enjoy the
That service I use and I get to make like a hundred more songs. I think
I'm trying to order some coffee right now
What up, deal
I can't hold it
Banana coffee. Have you heard of banana coffee?
A hint of tropical flavor.
That sounds pretty good. Banana coffee.
Have you heard of that?
I love Vietnamese coffee places. They're really, really good.
Let me see, so let me see.
Jeremy Cowboy, shout out to you. He already knows.
Banana coffee, I've never tried that. I've never tried that brother. Was it like banana seeds or like like how they catch up flavor
artificial
No, let me look at it. It's no it's like a boba house. I think it's not I don't know if it's boba though
It's let me see it says they've always kind of like
Delicious coffees and you see being give me a copy of tropical flavor as if sipping a comforting treat while taking the scenic beauty of Vietnam's highlands
Okay, sounds fine
Let's do it
Yeah, avocado coffee, you know, it sounds kind of gross
So you hit the ill part I thought about it might be
Let's see so it has black sugar boba locking knock I want to think with hi-cap
Google the worst coffee in the in the world
One of the most expensive coffee sounds like the worst, it's from Africa and it's like
pooped out by some bird, like the coffee de-grounds are and then they make the coffee, I think
it's a bird or cat.
When they eat the plant, the seeds fertilize in the gut and when they ship it out it becomes
more nutrients.
Yeah, well this yeah, and the seeds don't digest and so they can drop seeds and then the seeds are into
That's what basically a coffee the coffee bean is. I guess they were a coffee beans. They probably got highest fucking in this coffee
You see like birds me coffee beans. You know, why don't you just I get corn?
Mmm, so salt and milk
Regular sweet, okay, that sounds good 20 bucks. Okay
psyche knows a lot of answers psyche. Why don't why don't why don't people digest corn?
Because of this because of the casing on it. It's like it's it's undigestible and so it just passes
through it's like a kernel. I don't know if it has to do with it even if even if we make chew on it
and pop the casing. Why doesn't it just be like chewed up again? I mean it's like that part of
it doesn't digest it's just like it will just be like a little like a
So when the inside will digest and the outside skin will shit out raw
Yeah, no matter what it looks like. Yeah
Let's see. Okay. Oh
Okay, I'm getting a special coffee tonight. I'm sorry
Okay, I'm getting it banana coffee and salted moose cream whatever
Yeah, banana coffee sounds good. I love I like the Vietnamese. I'll be back. I make some moves. Okay. Oh, hey, wait
What's this? What's thank you Arbiter Arbiter? Thank you ghost
Arbiter ghost. I missed it. Thank you ghost. Look at ghost. Okay. Nice guy. Wait, wait, wait. Donate
Yeah, again, thank you so much. I mean, let me know if you want another dad another panel goes that's or yeah
So thank you so much. I didn't see that. I'm so sorry. I missed that. Thank you so much
And I didn't mean to like you said that money talk man. So that money to shout out shout out shout out to ghost man
He's an awesome child, but if we gonna donate shout out to him
Jamie Cowboys to you already know Jamie
Let's go
You should be up here talking
Thank you sponsor whenever you want. Okay. Thank you so much
I'll do it goes
Show I mean, I don't just say no, I'll do a ghost show, you know for sure. So you I'll do that
There'll be a ghost show
Okay, the ghost though
We should be
It's a ghost. Oh, yeah, they just put just put three hour live
Sponsored by ghosts
Yeah
Yeah, they're basically two and a half hours a three hour lives. Yep. Yep. Okay
Let's see. Yeah, I have this really funny lot on wallpaper curated images
Okay, I have a lot of these AI photos of myself I'm gonna start putting in
He said is your money now do whatever you want
thank you thank you goes appreciate you appreciate you very much goes has been
here since the beginning basically the the show you know I'm the first guest
okay so Alexander but it was I was watching I didn't join the panel too
I was watching looking at a desk
I've I've announced my guys. I'm working on the panel the panel verse tarot. Okay. I'm gonna do this panel verse tarot
It will be things around the panel verse
I you know, it'd be kind of that theme. Oh, maybe but I'll show you the first card that I have I'm working on
I'm working on it right now. I have the fools on hold on. I'll show you the fool
some vertical
A segment of Trevor and then just this and it and then go live and then just have like conversations with people
Well, yeah, I mean, I'll do it between the I'll do it between the sponsor panels and thinking but here's the here's the
Here I'll put myself in the middle and here's the card. I here's the first card. So what do you guys think?
Good
Laughing there's me
With the microphones and then there's the the cats and there's me butterflies and there's like the
like that
So what you're trying to do is like take take the picture of the deck
Uploaded and when when the car comes out you're gonna put the picture
No, I mean, um, no, this is I mean, I'm just I'm just I'm working with the AI
In designing the deck and then I will you know, I'll have like the entire deck done
I'm just gonna do like one part of the blind deck. I was telling you about on Amazon. They create your own. Okay. Yeah
And then, and then it's, but I'm working with it on like, like, the AI understands like my show because I, I just got so with the AI, so it knows about the show and stuff like that.
And so it's, and I'll tell it about people and you know, it's about people that I've written songs about stuff because I've read the songs too.
And so it remembers that information and it will.
it comes up with ideas too about like oh so I knew it came up with the kind of the
panel verse theme I was like oh that's a good idea but it's like really into like
it's kind of funny it's just like it's kind of like things like I think a
little bit but you know a lot like smarter and more talented. The cat is gonna be
reading terrors while singing it to you.
Yeah, well, but it suggested that to us. I said, you know, they said how I have the cats choose the tarot have you know
I'm and or different little cute things like it has like little lines for like Rudy and Lenore and stuff
It's so funny. It's like, you know, it's exactly and I don't even ask him to say it
It's just like it just comes up with some of those stuff. It's like
It's pretty funny. It is a kind of a flatterer. You have to watch out the chat GPT is very flattering if you tell it you have an idea
I will say it's like the best idea. It's very very friendly. I don't like that, but it's like I wanted
Not just told her it's a very very positive. I'll say it's very positive
But if you listen to the AI you think you were maybe smarter than it
Well, you know, we are
This service, um, yes, I need the battery that I faster than expected again. Okay
I'm gonna come back. I'm gonna come back late if anything. Yeah, okay. I'll see you later easy. Thank you so much
Thank you
Okay
So the monkeys eat the seeds yeah, there's a lot of stuff that
Why what are you doing? What are you doing now?
We're gonna talk about I don't know what do you guys talk about like you know, so what do you do for a living?
I don't know. Just I got a lot of shit in my mind. Are you criminal?
You've a lot of shit on your mind you said yeah, I got a lot of stuff on my mind
Um, do you want to share anything or ask any questions or maybe you want some?
I just know like like go into your panel and listen to your arm the stuff you say, you know what I mean?
uh-huh
Well, like what in particular I say a lot of stuff
You say a lot of stuff about um reading your arm
Dumped on the cards on stuff like that. I like stuff like that. You know what I mean?
cool
Yeah, oh, we've been a guest. It's welcome to the show. Oh
Hey, goes. Thank you very much. I appreciate you. Okay. We're good guy. What up, boss?
That brother idea
By the way, it's like I didn't want to
I didn't donate to extend anything if you do whatever you want with it. Okay. There's no
Just give me some money
I really appreciate you. That's nice of you, man. Very generous
But goes the way when you're
Yeah, oh you win if you win that round goes to win that
Well, I well I did win that's anybody else gonna donate. I guess I did win that one
How you doing brother?
Yeah, hey, did you watch the did you watch the dust and pure your fight and max all the way?
No, I didn't watch that yet
Happened Saturday night. Yeah, I've been doing a lot of stuff. Yeah
There's a good fight man, I'd recommend watching it especially I don't know if you like watching that shit
But if you if you like watching it, I definitely recommend it. I like boxing. I like kickboxing stuff, you know me and certain sports
you kind of seem like a person that might if you did like it you might watch it you might bet on it
Nah, I don't do betting. No
When you bet, you know you lose again. You get you gamble and you lose you don't got the money to pay
They they come and beat the heck out of you
Well, they can happen. Let's bet. Yeah, but a lot of people like are careful
Yeah, that's a lot of a lot of people don't have money and they do that stuff. I mean
Yeah, I got to watch out for this one, but when you got like fucking your money and like you got a little bit of money
To do whatever you want with it and you bet a little bit. I mean it could pay off, but
9 and a half 9.8 times out of 10. It's not gonna pay off
Gambling
Yeah
Pretty much agree, but you know, I mean, I guess some people have one, of course
You know, but it's like the odds are with the casino always, you know
The best chances are with actually the scratcher tickets. I always win psyche
The house always wins, but yeah, but sometimes it doesn't you know, it's like it
Sometimes it doesn't so it doesn't always it does a lot of
Well, I also have I have money to spend too. So like that's a different skill
Yeah, that'd be different if you're not going there betting your last $10 on it
But if you got a little bit of money to spend I mean
Yeah, and some people do but the problem is people people look will go all in those so they'll start getting like obsessed and stuff like that
Okay, so people are addicted to I've never understood that people are addicted to that shit. How are you gonna be addicted to losing money?
Well, it's not losing money. It's like addicted to the gate to the to the prospect of
The thought of winning you know the thought of winning. It's like, you know, it's like
So you might lose but it's like, you know, you go in thinking that it's like, you know, you're lucky or something so
This like I got an argument the other night psyche, which it wasn't on your panels on a different one, but a girl
She's like oh you have an extra ten dollars wouldn't you want to pay me for my only pants?
I was like I would rather give the homeless dude
Ten bucks because at least that means something like I gave him a ten bucks
Makes not your only fans I'd rather get the homeless the man that lives like he's up
He's literally up the street. I'd rather get him ten bucks
Right. I mean, it's like, yeah, you can put things into you.
That's a question I want to ask you.
Psyche and you and girls, because you are on the panel.
Yeah, go ahead.
That's a question.
When you know how people, you know how kids get bullied in school,
and then sometimes, I know what to suspect to you, panel.
I don't want to, like, disrespect your panel,
but you know how kids get bullied,
and sometimes the kids take their life away
because they get tired getting bullied, right?
That's wrong.
Yeah.
yeah I think that's wrong I think I don't want to be what you asked me I
think if you had a good father figure in your life
Like because boy, it's almost good in a way like you're gonna get tougher. You can take these way out
We're gonna say I'm like certain kids certain kids can't handle that. Yeah, a lot of kids can't handle that
I see a lot of kids. Well, that's the difference. Can you get can you get rid of bullying? I mean, it's gonna be hard to do
Can you can your son
Can you teach your son to be stronger than that bullying like fuck them?
Yeah, that's right. I'm not gonna take my own life. Yeah effects. Yeah, but now but you know some kids get on the internet
It's not all about getting beat up
Or it's stuff what people say to kids on the internet like cyberbullying
All that stuff, you know, some people take their life because of that that's stupid reason
I know they do and it's it's exactly what he said. It's a stupid reason
That's why we got a you got to be especially for older and you have like son or something
You got to be a father figure in their life like shit's gonna happen. They got to be stronger than that
Yeah, that's fast. This is my daughter used to get both school and I told my daughter
You need to man up and I tell you what I would have put you in and said I tell her down to put her in boxing
Mustins, that's what I would done
One day the girl she my daughter got tired the girls bully on my damn my dad
Yeah, she fought back. Did she fight back? Yeah, my daughter grabbed the ball
Exactly. Yeah, they was on jumper and my other daughter jumped in on the fight
I'm trying to teach my brother. I don't have a son, but I do have a little brother
I'm teaching that you're I'm teaching about like debating the stuff
But he's also in boxing too and I but you I said Jessica you have them hands. You got no when to throw them other doctors
But they debate them talk, you know, like even if they want to argue whatever walkway
You got no when to throw them other doctors. You know I'm saying yeah, that's five
You right on that. It's not like a it's not like a prison mine state where you go there and find the biggest motherfucker
And you punch them and all of a sudden you're not gonna get picked on bro. You're in high school dog fucking
Yeah, that's right there
Yeah, you debate them debate the fuck out of them, but they want a little peace brother
Yeah, you've got demands. Hey keep them back keep them back, but once they unlike that gate, let me go
Yep
Yeah, I just started a question correctly in my bed. Yeah, that is just like I just like that shit. You know, I mean I
Just like bullying but I mean, I guess I've never been in the mind of a bully
I don't know what they're thinking when they're back down the world. I'm saying like yeah
I say like this. It's like the arm the parents didn't teach the kids not to do that shit. I mean
Isn't that kind of weird? It's inhuman nature to bully though. Like it is, but it is but why why do that to somebody?
And then when you get older, well, I think way back in the day because uh
Hunter and gatherer days like they they're not a hunter. They're not gonna gather for you
So I guess maybe that would like bully them out of the pack
But if that was the case only the strong would survive so we should all be strong at this point
That's a social Darwinism too, and that's like which is kind of can be kind of ugly. That is true. Yeah
So someone
Hey boys like you want to if anybody pays to kick me off. That's fine. I don't want to sponsor any
I just that's your money. Do whatever you want. I don't want to sponsor me either
Unless you want to spot unless you wanted to sponsor something. Thank you so much
Ooh that's
Let's be that
And you wish it was a beta and it wasn't he did say that he literally said that
Well, yes, what's good man, that's me the right there on the screen looks like her, huh?
Oh god, turn it off. Turn it off. She's putting on a spell on all your motherfuckers
I'm the devil yeah, hey God you heard God, you know devil you know devil LDS, too. You're a good dude
Am I a good dude
You buy your way you buy your way into it about half ass by half ass ten ten bucks caught you ten bucks
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
God
I'm inspiring inspiring enter entrepreneurs and in all kinds of ideas right guys by the way
It's like you fucked up and you said earlier
You said like oh ghost has been here from the beginning and then you said all of this dream
But I've been here since the beginning
Streaming oh, you were here before I started streaming before I did the live streams one. No listen to what I'm listening what I'm saying though
Because you guys you know what happened you guys try to call me fucking
All these things and I've been here always. Yeah, I know
Then put a little respect on Ghostname Yard
And I listen back to his voice and it's not you for sure
I just listen back very carefully not even on the point. Well, listen, I would I would out debate that man any day
Yeah
Good good good. Well, I mean, I know you got anybody see that he was on with I think he was on it
I'm a show with Kate today. He's on his channel. I don't know if it's all of that
No, listen, let Alex up. I'm sponsoring the another
I'm sponsoring the panel. Let Alex up. Okay. Where's Alex totally on totally just kidding by the way
Imagine that that you crashed out. He is he not just like he's literally a crash out
Yeah, well he crashed out last night really hard like it was like Alex he crashes out every time I talk to the man
He crashes out
There's no one with Alex it's like literally it's not zero through ten literally ten every time I talk to him, it's ten
Dan
He'll put a he'll put a he'll put a hit on me and I'll be sleeping with the fishes so no Sebastian
Yeah, but I wouldn't look like that beard. Oh my god. That's looking good, brother. Okay. Thank you. I think I like it brother
I think just to derange him. I don't think you would even mind if I like that full beard
You got the whole thing going on. I like it. Thank you. Yeah, my glasses my beard
Very I didn't say I like your hair. I like the glass. I like the beard. No, you don't care. Okay
No, I would I would I would scope it up a little bit. So it's fucking it back. I'd put it up a little bit
You know I'm gonna do goes
I'm gonna take my question. I'm gonna make an emoji on my age of a ghost and that will be you
You already draw you already drew me
Yeah, okay, but I'm gonna do another picture of a ghost. I would be honored. I would be honored
That you know, it's ghosts and then it's like, you know, it's like, you know
And then it can be me. You mean it can mean anything, right? But it's like, you know, just remember like I'd be honored
Sir at the idea when
Yeah, I mean when you came on and you know, we're so nice. Okay, so it goes clip art
Let's see. Oh, I can I can because everyone is expecting me like oh the burden of whoop-a-boo on you dumb dumb
I'm gonna crash out dumb dumb. That's what they're all expecting
Do you guys like this one? Yeah, guys, did you like this one? Hold on this one or?
Oh that looks better
Like that one. I think this one. Yeah, I like it
Let's see if I can put it in there. I
Should have I should be able to have like I don't know how many emojis I can have now
But I can have quite a few I think okay, so save the photos
Okay, and then I can go oh shit
Super phones not charging right and then I'm gonna pull it right for the guys
Okay, so I'm gonna go to
Okay badge emoji
I'm gonna take guys. I'm taking away temporarily the the you know the members badge
I'm just gonna put it on YouTube badge for just now. Okay. Um, this isn't I'm not doing it because of Canada dry
I don't want to use any of his art because it's bad juju for my show. Okay, so
Yeah, no bad future
Yeah, he was on saying that I was I was eating my own vomit or something like that something kind of disgusting thing
Okay, so as a as you gain more members, you're gonna upload and share even more
So I need 18 more members to done anymore. So I have to delete something. Okay, so I'm gonna delete
the
LOL because people can just type LOL and I'll put the ghost to replace the image. Yeah, sir
Hey, the people's podcast, how do you feel about that psyche is putting
What's up? How do you feel about that? How do you feel about him putting that in there the the girls?
Well, how do you feel about that?
You told my back side?
I'm not putting it on my members for members. It's okay. So I put it in. Yes, sir
How do you know about that the people's podcast?
Tablets died of blessed. I'll put it up. I promise keep up the great lives. Oh, thank you easy. Thank you so much
Yeah, I'm hoping I get my coffee soon. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Hey Trevor
By the way, the people's pot is not like a why we've been saying that is not like a a matrimonial thing
Yeah, but you're a ghost you part of the people's podcast too
It's in your name you retard it's in your name
Literally look underneath your name assess the people's podcast
Yeah, that's what he means. He's like, he's like, why do you have the people?
That's not even a thing anymore. So why why why is that in your name?
What
Why is your name underneath your name? Why does it say the people's podcast that's non-existent?
I represent it. Well, we got probably represent what you represent. So you represent nothing because it's nothing
I remember that the people podcast. What's up?
Which is nothing it's no more there isn't
You think that's what you think well
Yeah, that's what I think go ahead and prove me wrong. No, I'm saying that's not I'm not getting mad about it
You know me. That's what what you think. You know me is no more. That's what you think
Go ahead and prove me wrong. It's not existent
Well, you sure you positive. I'm pretty positive. Yeah, well you came up on that panel a couple times, bro
I have but it's not existing anymore. Yes, it is. I know it's not existing anymore
You don't see the backup you don't see you don't know you don't see the other panel the backup panel
No, I don't see nothing
You know part of the people podcast
You pop up you pop them on the panel to so they went once a week now
There's none a week. It's not it's not it's not like I'm getting mad. It's you know, I mean, I really don't care what you say
You know me
Yeah, because you make the same as arguments on that podcast, which I've talked to you before.
Yeah, it makes no sense at all.
You don't have it.
You've never, oh yeah, you've never.
What do you say to me?
You punked me?
What do you do to me?
I said you said you punked me, right?
You said you punked me.
I never once said that.
Go ahead and punk me right now, boy.
See what I'm going to do.
I'm going to fucking dick.
That's what y'all do all fucking day.
Who's that?
Honest.
You let him in.
Get a job.
Who is that?
Go fucking do a hobby.
Go fucking buy a beer at a soup kitchen.
We're talking to you ladies.
What are you talking about?
She's talking to the ghosts.
Okay
Yeah, if you want a little piece
I would love a little piece from that bitch.
Ghost is not like that. Ghost is not like that.
No, it's like that. I'll take you and her.
By the way, you're trying to defend the people's party.
Let's run that shit.
I want all the smoke, brother.
You just want to start an argument like you always do, bro.
Yes, sir, I do.
She knows this broke-ass, bone-ass, bozo-nigger ghost.
God, shut the fuck up, boy.
But, God, by the way, since I had to send $10,
You can't send $10 fucking retard
You should send out $10 or $10. I wait my fucking thing a kick you're
Here you don't have the fuck you're talking about
You're too stupid to have the conversation
Yeah, cuz you're God. I'm what God's gonna get kick. I'm here. Kick me motherfucker. Kick me good 25 bucks
Big all right. Well, I gotta give another 25 bucks to do it. Yeah. Yeah, damn. It's gonna be 15
Another 25 reach into your fucking little purse
It looks 25 dollars
Pull out two tens and a five and fucking shoot that fucking author 25. I can do it do it
Go 25 to somebody comes. Well, you listen. Here's my thing. I'll throw it
Not to kick you, but if somebody I'll throw 25 if you let people over here that actually has an argument
I'll throw 25 down
I'll do it immediately
Yeah, I'll let anybody up here. I'll let anybody up
I'm not trying to kick anybody. I just want an argument. Okay. Okay. I'll get it on
Fuck you're talking about
Oh
Next argument he fucking lost this one next
goes
Sir, you don't know how I happen
Go to white. Would you like me? Are you a small word man?
Would you like me to explain how to make an argument?
Glass you see through that mother shit
You like John I want what I thought those was cool
You got a nasty mouth
What did I say that was nasty and tell me cuz I'll
Say cuz I'll
Women that's for sure. Yeah, you say you don't like woman. What's up with that ghost? I've never once said I don't like women
I love women. You hate women. I hate women. You said never once said I hate it women go in for
I love women
Well, I'd never
Yes, you did you said it last night. I think gobers done though. All right. Let's run it. All right. Go ahead
How because I'm a burn your ass up when you when you step in stupid. All right. Go ahead. I said I hate it women
You hate it. I said I hate a woman. We know you hate women. I know you hate women. It's true proof that how do I hate women?
On three examples. I've seen you hate all women for no reason. No, right? This is how I hate women
I'm gonna go ahead and explain yourself
To go two months ago on TPP you in grace. You were grace remember grace you having a conversation with grace on the panel
You didn't let her fucking say a fucking where you kept calling her a bitch you heard bitch
You're hurt you're hurt. Oh, she is a bitch. She is a bitch. What's the problem?
She was being all nice to you and you started calling her a bitch for no reason. That's one and that means I hate women
Strike two was about a month ago. You were over here on psyches panel
It was you Alexander fucking easy and what's your name was here Christine was here
And you a fucking dog and Christina or like some fucking old shoe, man
You would shoot her you
So that means, does that mean that I
Does that mean that
But how does that, you got a
Listen, sir, you just took the position
Listen, sir, it's my turn to talk, by the way
That's two strikes, that's two strikes, that's right
Fuck it, give me three strikes, I don't give a fuck
Does that mean I hate women? How does that mean I hate women?
Third strike was life
So I disrespected thrusting
I disrespected some random ass women.
How does that mean I hate women?
You know, why are you suspecting dummy?
We had rage and we had spunky up here.
They're all showing their tits, alright?
You had a big fucking problem with that, alright?
Disgusting degenerate.
Yeah, exactly. You hate women.
You hate women. That's three strikes. You out!
Cuz everybody enjoyed
No, no chicks just and you like touching kids you see how it's like
Mess up psyches panel
You don't give a fuck he thinks that $10 is immunity. Yeah, well, I mean, you know what I'm gonna do
I'm just gonna resort resort because I just want to make sure everything's good. So good night guys
You like what you did motherfucker good work